[
    [
        "Take a stroll along the Prunus-Petai Trail, a 2km boardwalk close to the entrance of MacRitchie Reservoir Park. You'll be rewarded with beautiful views of the calm forest against the backdrop of dense forest, and close-up sightings of various plants and wildlife, including the Singapore Rhododendron, clouded monitor lizards and orange-bellied squirrels.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    24,
                    42,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    85,
                    110,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Nestled along Mackenzie Road, the cafe can be easily spotted from afar, thanks to a giant curry puff planted right outside the store.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    14,
                    28,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "An angry Facebook user reported a case of a cut sustained (on the face) by her 14 year old niece at the latest attraction - Mirror Maze, located at Jewel Changi Airport.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    124,
                    135,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    148,
                    168,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    9,
                    17,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The SLA, which has been managing Turf City since 1999, leases the site for lifestyle and recreational uses on an interim basis.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    4,
                    7,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    33,
                    42,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "A two-station extension to Marina Bay opened on 14 January 2012.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    27,
                    37,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "For example, he noted that it is only a 10-minute drive to the Central Business District and the prime Orchard Road shopping belt.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    63,
                    88,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    103,
                    115,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "On 25 May 1961, a small fire started innocuously enough in a makeshift squatter hut lying on its fringe - a hillside at Kampong Tiong Bahru Road. However, powerful winds that day caused it to escalate into a roaring blaze, carving a sweeping path of destruction. Ferocious flames, further fuelled by oil and petrol from the area's godowns, leapt rather easily across the road to Kampong Bukit Ho Swee.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    120,
                    144,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    379,
                    400,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Two stations, Xilin MRT station and Sungei Bedok MRT station, will be added to the Downtown Line, with Sungei Bedok as an interchange station with the Thomson-East Coast line.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    14,
                    31,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    36,
                    60,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    83,
                    96,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    103,
                    115,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    151,
                    174,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "On 17 January 2013, then-Minister for Transport Lui Tuck Yew announced 'Circle Line Stage 6' which will 'close the circle', set to be completed by 2025.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    72,
                    83,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "This was the third blaze that firefighters had to battle in one night, following separate incidents hours earlier in Bedok and Tampines.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    117,
                    122,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    127,
                    135,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "In the boys' final, it was business as usual for Catholic High School (CHS) who retained their B Division title after beating YTSS 3-2. It was a case of deja vu for CHS' Arifin Zulkarnain, who also played in the decider in last year's finals against Maris Stella High School.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    49,
                    69,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    71,
                    74,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    126,
                    130,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    165,
                    168,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    250,
                    274,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "A new lawn and lookout deck in East Coast Park now offers East Coast residents additional space for recreational activities.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    31,
                    46,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    58,
                    68,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "That is the address of J Gateway condominium.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    23,
                    32,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "It's also pretty close to Lower Peirce Reservoir, which connects to Windsor Nature Park that connects all the way to MacRitchie Nature Park and the whole central water catchment area.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    26,
                    48,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    68,
                    87,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    117,
                    139,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "On 27 April 2007, then Transport Minister Raymond Lim announced that the Downtown Line would be built in three stages stretching 40 kilometres (25 mi) with 33 stations.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    73,
                    86,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "When operations assistant Sally Tng craves Chinese soups with steamed rice, she would frequent her favourite stall at Amoy Street Food Centre in Chinatown.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    118,
                    141,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    145,
                    154,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "In addition, service roads were constructed along the expressway near Toa Payoh and at the Woodsville interchange.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    70,
                    79,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    91,
                    101,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Prior to hospital admission, he had gone to work at Philemon Singapore, which is at 16 Kallang Place. He lives at Rivervale Drive.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    52,
                    70,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    84,
                    100,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    114,
                    129,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Exit A and Exit E of Choa Chu Kang station is linked to Lot One.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    6,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    11,
                    17,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    21,
                    42,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    56,
                    63,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "In this example, there are a few bus routes (922, 972, 976) from Bukit Panjang Interchange.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    65,
                    90,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "After the Branch line (from the Jurong East to Choa Chu Kang stations) opened in 1990, the Woodlands MRT line was envisioned so as to close the gap between Yishun and Choa Chu Kang stations.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    10,
                    21,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    32,
                    43,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    47,
                    68,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    91,
                    109,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    156,
                    162,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    167,
                    188,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "This stall at Hillion Mall did not provide me with a receipt plus HPB QR Code even though I ordered a healthy meal which consisted of Brown Rice and 2 servings of vegetables (long beans and Kai-Lan).",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    14,
                    26,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    66,
                    69,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The linkway will serve as many as 50 housing blocks, or about 8,000 households, in the area.",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "The four-level Sengkang station is an integrated hub with the three modes of transport - MRT, LRT and bus - serving the Sengkang area.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    15,
                    31,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    89,
                    92,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    94,
                    97,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    120,
                    128,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "WC Tham is at Blk 6 Tanjong Pagar Plaza Hawker Centre. Loading/Unloading Lot Became Private Parking Lot..!!?",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    14,
                    53,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "When Mr Brian Lim was still a student several years ago, he was on a plane to Indonesia and seated next to a woman who was struggling to read and fill in her immigration form. Mr Lim, 31, who teaches English at Bukit Panjang Government High School, said he tells his students the story about the woman on the plane to remind them that English is not just a subject in school or another exam to pass but something that will impact their lives.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    78,
                    87,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    211,
                    247,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "His neighbour was pouring unknown fluid down from his HDB unit at Blk 612B Punggol Drive, Singapore 822612 , Damai Grove estate.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    66,
                    88,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    90,
                    106,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    109,
                    120,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    54,
                    57,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Urban planning in Singapore is the direction of infrastructure development in Singapore.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    18,
                    27,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    78,
                    87,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "On Feb 23, the driver of a forklift at the site of a BTO project in Tampines North died after he was thrown out of the vehicle, which had toppled on its side.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    68,
                    82,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Get Together Coffee Shop (177 Bukit Batok West Avenue 8, Singapore 650177 )is located 15 minutes away by bus from Bukit Batok MRT Station, which is unfortunately not very convenient. However, if you live in the West, this beats travelling halfway across Singapore to satisfy your hawker cravings!",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    24,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    26,
                    55,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    57,
                    73,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    114,
                    137,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    254,
                    263,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Prior to hospital admission, she had gone to work at Lonza Biologics - located at 35 Tuas South Avenue 6 - and visited had Bugis Junction.She lives in the Aljunied Road area.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    53,
                    68,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    82,
                    104,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    123,
                    137,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    155,
                    168,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Originally planned as three separate lines, the lines merged into the Downtown Line in 2007 and construction began in three stages.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    70,
                    83,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Two new stations will be added on the North South line.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    38,
                    54,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "A watercolour painting of Beo Crescent, one of the estates which rose following the Bukit Ho Swee fire, as depicted by Singaporean watercolourist Ong Kim Seng.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    26,
                    38,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    84,
                    97,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "SBS Transit has three depots: Sengkang Depot houses trains for the North East line, the Sengkang LRT line, and the Punggol LRT line.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    30,
                    44,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    67,
                    82,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    88,
                    105,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    115,
                    131,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The Marina Mandarin was rebranded as the luxurious Parkroyal Collection Marina Bay. Two Six Senses properties have been renamed The Maxwell Reserve and The Duxton Reserve, under Marriott's Autograph Collection range. Also, boutique hotels KeSa House and Wanderlust - the latter is in Little India - both reopened in March under The Unlimited Collection by Oakwood, a new brand. Boutique hotel Wanderlust in Little India reopened in March under The Unlimited Collection by Oakwood, a new brand.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    4,
                    19,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    51,
                    82,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    88,
                    98,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    128,
                    147,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    152,
                    170,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    178,
                    186,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    239,
                    249,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    254,
                    264,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    284,
                    296,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    328,
                    352,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    356,
                    363,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    393,
                    403,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    407,
                    419,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    444,
                    468,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    472,
                    479,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "As the name implies, the fully-underground 20-kilometre (12 mi) North East line runs from the Central Area to the northeastern parts of the island.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    64,
                    79,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    94,
                    106,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The existing S.E.A. Aquarium will expand thrice its current size and be rebranded as the Singapore Oceanarium.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    13,
                    28,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    89,
                    109,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Not long after, the imposing Wisma Geylang Serai comes into view as the cab turns into Engku Aman Road. Serving as the Geylang Serai precinct community civic and cultural centre, the design of this sprawling brown-and-white complex draws inspiration from various heritage elements, including serai fronds, folded ketupat leaves and the traditional Malay house serambi or verandah.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    29,
                    48,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    87,
                    102,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    119,
                    132,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Blk 506 onwards heading Bedok Town Secondary School (Westwards towards Jalan Eunos) belongs to Aljunied GRC. Blk 401 onwards and that side of the road all belong to East Coast GRC other than those specified as Fengshan. Borderline is divided between Bedok North Road.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    7,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    24,
                    51,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    71,
                    82,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    95,
                    107,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    109,
                    116,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    165,
                    179,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    210,
                    218,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    250,
                    266,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "If you don't mind the travel time the food court at Marin Square is a good place to sit and study.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    52,
                    64,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The Weights and Measures Office said on Feb 11 that the weighing instruments at FairPrice's NEX and AMK Hub branches have been inspected and verified to be accurate.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    4,
                    31,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    80,
                    90,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    92,
                    95,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    100,
                    107,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The residential component, named One Holland Village Residences, offers a total of 296 residential units split into three blocks.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    33,
                    63,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Singapore has no natural lakes, but reservoirs and water catchment areas have been constructed to store fresh water for Singapore's water supply.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    9,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    120,
                    129,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Upon arrival at Anderson Bridge, newly pedestrianised for 2022, walk halfway across and look to the right along Queen Elizabeth Walk on the water's edge. Named for the Coronation in 1952, this area was the site of the famous Satay Club from 1970 to 1995; it then moved to Clarke Quay, and then Gardens by the Bay. As you leave Anderson Bridge, look back. The brown stone plaque commemorates construction in 1909 and states the stone is from Assouan in Egypt; why? Because the Anderson Bridge contractor, Sir John Aird, also constructed the Old Aswan Dam on the Nile in 1902.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    16,
                    31,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    112,
                    132,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    225,
                    235,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    272,
                    283,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    294,
                    312,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    327,
                    341,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    441,
                    448,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    452,
                    457,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    476,
                    491,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    540,
                    553,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    561,
                    565,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Ong said that while the island was no longer inhabited by civilians, the names of the old kampongs live on in training areas, such as Selabin, Permatang and San Yong Kong.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    134,
                    141,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    143,
                    152,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    157,
                    170,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "There's plenty of space around Portsdown Avenue for one, with the undeveloped area around the back of Alexandra Hospital.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    31,
                    47,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    102,
                    120,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Seletar Airport is Singapore's first civil aviation airport and is primarily used for private aviation.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    15,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    19,
                    28,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "At this time, Singapore faced an urgent need for environmental management and to control land use.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    14,
                    23,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The property will also appeal to families with school-going children because it is near schools like Temasek Primary, Temasek Secondary and Temasek Junior College. Victoria School and Victoria Junior College are also within 3km of the development.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    101,
                    116,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    118,
                    135,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    140,
                    162,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    164,
                    179,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    184,
                    207,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The National Gallery Singapore is a fantastic art gallery! Huge and great collection, and it's a unique building built around the Old City Hall and Supreme Court. One of my recommended things to do in Singapore.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    4,
                    30,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    130,
                    143,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    148,
                    161,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    201,
                    210,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The Fullerton Hotel is immediately on the right. The Fullerton Building once housed the General Post Office (GPO), which had many innovative features; one was a mail drop to a basement conveyor that ran along a tunnel under Fullerton Road to a pier for direct loading onto ships bound for India and England.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    4,
                    19,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    53,
                    71,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    88,
                    107,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    109,
                    112,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    224,
                    238,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    289,
                    294,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    299,
                    306,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "You get discounted rates if you are a member of Aranda Country Club or NTUC. Address: 60 Pasir Ris Drive 3 Singapore 519497",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    48,
                    67,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    71,
                    75,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    86,
                    123,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Choa Chu Kang is bisected by the Kranji Expressway (KJE), seperating the northern subzones of Limbang and Yew Tee from the southern subzones of Choa Chu Kang Central, Peng Siang, Keat Hong and Teck Whye.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    13,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    33,
                    50,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    52,
                    55,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    94,
                    101,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    106,
                    113,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    144,
                    165,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    167,
                    177,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    179,
                    188,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    193,
                    202,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The northern terminus of Woodlands North is expected to interchange with the Johor Bahru-Singapore Rapid Transit System to provide access to Johor Bahru and the future Iskandar Malaysia Bus Rapid Transit.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    25,
                    40,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    77,
                    119,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    141,
                    152,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    168,
                    203,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Senior Minister of State for Health, and Communications and Information, Dr Janil Puthucheary, who is an MP for Pasir Ris-Punggol GRC, said at the topping-up ceremony yesterday that while construction was delayed because of the pandemic, it is on track to open progressively.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    112,
                    133,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The section of the expressway between Adam Road and Whitley Road was completed by 1978 and was opened to traffic in 1979.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    38,
                    47,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    52,
                    64,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "A section of the road above a construction site near Holland Road caved in on the morning of 24 May 2008, creating a hole.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    53,
                    65,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "ParkView @ Bidadari, while within a respectable five-minute walking distance to Woodleigh MRT on the North-East Line (NEL), requires a little more effort to get to.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    19,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    80,
                    93,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    101,
                    116,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    118,
                    121,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "This will result in the terminus to be shifted from the current Bukit Panjang MRT station to Sungei Kadut MRT station.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    64,
                    89,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    93,
                    117,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Mr Chia Boon Cheok supplies ice-cream bars to independent hawkers like Mr Chieng Puay Chui at an HDB block in Kim Tian Road.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    97,
                    100,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    110,
                    123,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "While eating my ramen at Ajisen @ Punggol Waterway Point, then found a price tag ticket inside my bowl.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    25,
                    31,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    34,
                    41,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    42,
                    56,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "East Coast Park is just a few minutes' drive from NÂ°18 making it a convenient green space to exercise, engage in water sports, or soak in the scenic coastline.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    15,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    50,
                    54,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Hua Yi Secondary removed mid-year exams for the Secondary 1 to Sec 3 levels in 2019, followed by Sec 4 and Sec 5 in 2020.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    16,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Because of this, there are several entrances to the forest; we found that the best one is located right by the bus stop opposite Ngee Ann Polytechnic.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    129,
                    149,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The six-storey Radin Mas CC also boasts new facilities such as a performing arts studio and a culinary studio.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    15,
                    27,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "In 2015, he took up a grant by Tuas Power Generation to study at NUS School of Engineering, today the NUS College of Design & Engineering",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    31,
                    52,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    65,
                    68,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    69,
                    90,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    102,
                    105,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    106,
                    137,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "To add bonus, Lee Yi Shyan as Chai Chee MP do not cover HDB estates with Cha Chee X road name. Instead, it covers the square from Bedok North Ave 3, Bedok North Road & Bedok North Ave 1, effectively circling entire Bedok Central / Swimming Pool areas to Fengshan Primary.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    30,
                    39,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    73,
                    81,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    130,
                    147,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    149,
                    165,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    168,
                    185,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    215,
                    244,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    254,
                    270,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The Master Plan, intended for the medium term, comprises land use plans across Singapore, and is revised every five years, while the detailed plans, issued by agencies supervising certain aspects of urban development, plot out short-term development.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    79,
                    88,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "In 2018, Singapore was ranked second globally in terms of containerised traffic, with 36.6 million Twenty-Foot Equivalent Units (TEUs) handled, and is also the world's busiest hub for transshipment traffic.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    9,
                    18,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Situated above the North East MRT line's depot, the expansion will include a new train stabling area, a maintenance workshop, and three new traction power stations.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    19,
                    38,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Bigger Build-To-Order (BTO) flats in the non-mature estates of Hougang and Jurong East were more oversubscribed than those in mature estates in the Housing Board's third sales exercise of the year.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    63,
                    70,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    75,
                    86,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    148,
                    161,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Two special education schools serving students with mild intellectual disability will move to an expanded, co-located campus in 2025, the Ministry of Education (MOE) said on Thursday (Nov 5). They are Chaoyang School in Ang Mo Kio, which serves primary school students, and Tanglin School in Bukit Merah serving secondary school students.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    138,
                    159,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    161,
                    164,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    201,
                    216,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    220,
                    230,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    274,
                    288,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    292,
                    303,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The 100-year-old Cashin House at the edge of the shore will also be reconstructed for educational purposes with new facilities such as an exhibition space, seminar rooms, and a seaview terrace.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    17,
                    29,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The zoning of the site has been changed to a business park where the former commercial warehouse space, Big Box, will be redeveloped into Perennial Business City.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    138,
                    161,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    104,
                    111,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "In order to ensure that they stay competitive in the global market, Singapore shifted towards the development of industrial clusters in the 1990s.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    68,
                    77,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Every station has a Passenger Service Centre (PSC) at the concourse.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    20,
                    44,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    46,
                    49,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "In the late 1960s, increasing demand of water led the government to examine the feasibility of increasing the capacity of the Peirce Reservoir. A higher dam was then constructed upstream of the existing dam in 1970. The Upper Peirce Reservoir was completed in 1975 and officially opened by then Prime Minister Mr Lee Kuan Yew on 27 February 1977.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    126,
                    142,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    220,
                    242,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The opening of the Woodlands Extension introduced bolder pieces of artwork, such as a 4,000 kg sculpture in Woodlands.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    19,
                    38,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    108,
                    117,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "A massive fire in a Jurong industrial area raged for more than two hours and triggered loud explosions on Friday (June 21), killing one and leaving two people injured.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    20,
                    26,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "With full on-campus learning on the horizon, we reveal insider tips from Amelia Leong, Year Three, Yong Pung How School of Law; Tan Teck Wee, Year Three, Lee Kong Chian School of Business; Trevor Ng, Year Four, School of Computing and Information Systems; and Germaine Lee, Year Two, School of Social Sciences; on the top lifestyle changes students can adopt to prioritise their health and safety as they continue online learning for now and prepare for their return to campus in the coming months.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    99,
                    126,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    154,
                    187,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    211,
                    254,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    284,
                    309,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Before Contract 921 showed up, the Rochor Canal ran between Sungei Road and Rochor Canal Road - where today There's a big green patch. In principle it might have been easy, that the station could simply be built under the canal. There are already several examples, such as the portion of the KPE running under the Kallang River.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    35,
                    47,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    60,
                    71,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    76,
                    93,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    314,
                    327,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    292,
                    295,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Wild boars spotted mingling with public at The Rail Mall, along Upper Bukit Timah Road, nearby to Hillview estate.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    43,
                    56,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    64,
                    86,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    98,
                    106,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Singapore's transport policy developed shortly after independence during the history of Singapore because of frequent traffic congestion in the Central Area.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    9,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    144,
                    156,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    88,
                    97,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The delicious chicken hor fun (rice noodles) from Weng Kee Ipoh Hor Fun (#01-04) is also not to be missed, served with succulent fried chicken meat atop a mound of slippery rice noodles covered in a generous drizzle of gravy, this stall in Changi Village Hawker Centre never fails to draw a queue.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    50,
                    71,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    240,
                    268,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Round the bend at Upper Changi Road North into Cosford Road, you will see Johore Battery looming ahead. It is a full-sized replica built in 2002, based on the main British coastal artillery defence network on the north-eastern coast of Singapore.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    18,
                    41,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    47,
                    59,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    74,
                    88,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    236,
                    245,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Stage 1 of Downtown line opened on 22 December 2013 with its official opening made on 21 December 2013 by Prime Minister Lee Hsien Loong.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    11,
                    24,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Among the 11 international institutions, five will be locating their case management offices at Maxwell Chambers Suites, which will create the highest concentration of case management offices in the world. The five are the International Chamber of Commerce, International Court of Arbitration; Singapore International Arbitration Centre; Singapore International Mediation Centre; Permanent Court of Arbitration; and the World Intellectual Property Organisation Arbitration and Mediation Centre.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    96,
                    119,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    223,
                    256,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    258,
                    292,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    294,
                    336,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    338,
                    378,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    380,
                    410,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    420,
                    493,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The first section, Jalan Toa Payoh, was completed by 1969.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    19,
                    34,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Network and operationsServicesTrain services on the North South MRT line operates from approximately 5:30 am to around midnight daily.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    52,
                    72,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "A woman in Singapore ordered seven drinks from the Starbucks outlet at AMK Hub, but all the beverages were found spilled on the public pedestrian footpath near the delivery address without any explanation as the delivery rider became uncontactable after marking the order delivered.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    11,
                    20,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    51,
                    60,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    71,
                    78,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Alternatively, you can start at Windsor Nature Park, where It's only 2.5km to the entrance of the walk.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    32,
                    51,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "For now, it seems unlikely that there will be properties coming up along the Woodlands Waterfront.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    77,
                    97,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The trio from DPS International School, together with seven friends from school, decided to collect food donations from their schoolmates to donate to food charity Food From The Heart for distribution to the needy.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    14,
                    38,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    164,
                    183,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The 53rd case works at the National University of Singapore and is linked to the cluster at Grace Assembly of God church.He stayed mostly at home at Hillview Avenue and had not interacted with his NUS colleagues and students after the onset of symptoms.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    27,
                    59,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    92,
                    120,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    149,
                    164,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    197,
                    200,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Economic growth will be sustained through providing land to meet the needs of all industries, developing business parks, constructing four regional centres (Tampines, Seletar, Woodlands, Jurong East) and transforming the Marina Bay area into an international business hub.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    157,
                    165,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    167,
                    174,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    176,
                    185,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    187,
                    198,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    221,
                    231,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The other four stages follow suit, with Stage 2 from Springleaf to Caldecott on 28 August 2021, Stage 3 from Mount Pleasant to Gardens by the Bay in 2022 (excluding Mount Pleasant and Marina South, which will open at a later date), Stage 4 from Tanjong Rhu to Bayshore in 2024 and Stage 5 from Bedok South to Sungei Bedok in 2025.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    53,
                    63,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    67,
                    76,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    109,
                    123,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    127,
                    145,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    165,
                    179,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    184,
                    196,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    245,
                    256,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    260,
                    268,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    294,
                    305,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    309,
                    321,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Its closing will be batched with another confirmed list site, the Housing Board executive condominium parcel in Bukit Batok West Avenue 8.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    66,
                    79,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    112,
                    137,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "As a trial run, luggage racks were installed on the C751B trains to serve travellers on the Changi Airport branch line.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    92,
                    118,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Through our engagement and with feedback received from Nature Groups, we are studying how we could retain the proposed core conservation area, to possibly form an extension of Admiralty Park, as part of the plans.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    55,
                    68,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    176,
                    190,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "However, fewer than 10 stalls out of the 182 at Blk 115 Bukit Merah were open for business when The Straits Times visited at 8.30am.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    48,
                    67,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    96,
                    113,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "It's walking distance to Keat Hong LRT station, with amenities in the area that include a market at Blk 253, ITE College West, Keat Hong Community Club, Keat Hong Shopping Centre and a slew of schools.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    25,
                    46,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    100,
                    107,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    109,
                    125,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    127,
                    151,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    153,
                    178,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Alternatively, they could dig below Lazada One, but that might be a lot more troublesome compared to sticking to the roads.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    36,
                    46,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "A new polyclinic in Sembawang is slated to open by this year, while six others in Kaki Bukit, Khatib, Serangoon, Tampines North, Tengah and Yew Tee will open by 2026, according to ST.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    20,
                    29,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    82,
                    92,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    94,
                    100,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    102,
                    111,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    113,
                    127,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    129,
                    135,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    140,
                    147,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    180,
                    182,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "History buffs will love Poh Tiong Beo Temple (201 Toa Payoh Lorong 6, Singapore 319385). Ask the friendly staff about its interesting long history! Apparently, it dates back to the Sung Dynasty of ancient China. It was a shrine in a coolie den for Tong An immigrants in the 1930s and has evolved into the sanctuary of worship it is today.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    24,
                    44,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    46,
                    68,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    70,
                    86,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    205,
                    210,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Of course, you can't miss Yue Hwa Chinese Products on Eu Tong Sen Road.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    26,
                    50,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    54,
                    70,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Developed by Mapletree and Keppel Land, The Reef at King's Dock is a 429-unit condominium currently being built at Keppel Bay in Harbourfront.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    13,
                    22,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    27,
                    38,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    40,
                    63,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    115,
                    125,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    129,
                    141,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "However, the ageing system had undermined the rail reliability on the line, requiring the NSL to upgrade its signalling system.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    90,
                    93,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The Tuas West Extension of the East West Line, consisting of Gul Circle, Tuas Crescent, Tuas West Road, and Tuas Link stations, opened on 18 June 2017.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    4,
                    23,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    31,
                    45,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    61,
                    71,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    73,
                    86,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    88,
                    102,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    108,
                    117,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The uneasy political arrangement and disputes over Singapore's status within the federation played a big influence on the planning process and the formulation of the 1965 Master Plan.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    51,
                    60,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "On 16 April 2019, the Singapore Tourism Board announced a new 7-hectare integrated tourism development in Jurong Lake District, which will be built by 2026.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    22,
                    45,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    106,
                    126,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "An upcoming project is the partial pedestrianisation of Woodlands Ring Road, located between Woodlands Drive 63 and Woodlands Drive 71 (adjacent to Kampung Admiralty).",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    56,
                    75,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    93,
                    111,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    116,
                    134,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    148,
                    165,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Construction from Jalan Anak Bukit to Boon Lay Road was started in 1978.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    18,
                    34,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    38,
                    51,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Dedicated to Kali, the Hindu Goddess of power, Sri Veeramakaliamman Hindu Temple is this grand, intricately designed temple built in the South Indian architectural style. Its address is 141 Serangoon Road, Singapore 218042.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    47,
                    80,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    186,
                    204,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    206,
                    222,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Nanyang Polytechnic (NYP) has launched a diploma course in artificial intelligence (AI) and data engineering that will be co-developed and co-taught by industry professionals and its lecturers.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    19,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    21,
                    24,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "serangoon polyclinic will be served by exit C of serangoon station.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    20,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    39,
                    45,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    49,
                    66,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Located close to the iconic Katong Shopping Centre, the site is also about 10 minutes commute to the future Marine Parade MRT station on the Thomson East Coast Line. Haig Girls' School and Tanjong Katong Primary School are within 1km to 2km away.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    28,
                    50,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    108,
                    133,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    141,
                    164,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    166,
                    184,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    189,
                    218,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Located near Lentor MRT station, the new neighbourhood is planned around the existing hillock, which will be developed into the new Lentor Hillock Park.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    13,
                    31,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    132,
                    151,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The 56th level of ION Orchard, 218m above ground, allows anyone to admire the buildings that dot the country from up above. Admission into the Ion Sky observatory is free.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    18,
                    29,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    143,
                    162,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "It will serve West Coast, Tengah and Choa Chu Kang, besides just Jurong when originally announced in 2001.A study on the possible 7 km West Coast extension from Pandan Reservoir MRT station to Haw Par Villa MRT station on the Circle line is currently being conducted.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    14,
                    24,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    26,
                    32,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    37,
                    50,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    65,
                    71,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    135,
                    155,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    161,
                    189,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    193,
                    218,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    226,
                    237,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The main island of Singapore is connected to the other islands by ferryboat services.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    19,
                    28,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "NEA added that access control and interim fencing had also been removed at 10 other markets earlier in June, including Beo Crescent Market, Bukit Timah Market and Tanglin Halt Market.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    119,
                    138,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    140,
                    158,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    163,
                    182,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The clubhouse was announced in May last year and plans for the five-storey building were revealed on Saturday (Nov 10) at the atrium of Lot One Shoppers' Mall, where an exhibition showing artist impressions and a 3D model of the clubhouse were on display.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    136,
                    158,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "\"One of the draws of this high floor unit is its unblocked view of Marina Bay Sands,\" says Low. \"High floor units of such sizes are rarely available on the market.\" The other draw of Suntec City is the strong community of Chinese businesses that are located there, he adds. The common areas of the office towers at Suntec City were recently refurbished, bringing it in line with other new Grade-A office towers.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    67,
                    83,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    183,
                    194,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    315,
                    326,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Dr Ettikan Kandasamy Karuppiah, chief technologist for the Asia Pacific South region at California-based Nvidia, said it is working with NYP to develop a module on applied deep learning, as part of the course.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    59,
                    77,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    88,
                    98,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    105,
                    111,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    137,
                    140,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Overall, the LTMP 2040 aims to ensure the land transport system of Singapore is more seamless and convenient, inclusive, safer, and cleaner.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    67,
                    76,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "While tunneling works were completed on 13 November 2020, transport minister Ong Ye Kung announced that Punggol Coast station's completion would be delayed to 2024 due to delays from the COVID-19 pandemic.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    104,
                    125,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "First proposed as an LRT line when originally announced in 2001, the 20-kilometre (12 mi) Jurong Region Line has since been upgraded to be a medium capacity line after the project was revived in 2013.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    90,
                    108,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The Sunday Times visited the Chong Pang City Wet Market on Thursday (Feb 4) and the Teck Ghee Court Market and Food Centre on Friday (Feb 5).",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    29,
                    55,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    84,
                    122,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Announced on 16 July 2019, Singapore will be building its first dementia care village to care for dementia patients and improve their quality of life and residential options available to them.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    27,
                    36,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The biggest deal was for an entire strata floor of 13,111 sq ft on the ninth level of Samsung Hub, which was purchased by construction group Lee Kim Tah for $53.1 million in May. It translates to $4,050 psf, which is a new high in terms of psf price for the 999-year leasehold, 30-storey office tower at 3 Church Street in the CBD.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    86,
                    97,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    141,
                    152,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    304,
                    319,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    327,
                    330,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "They are linked to the 880,000 sq ft Suntec Mall as well as the Suntec Singapore Convention & Exhibition Centre, with 450,000 sq ft of customisable event space.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    37,
                    48,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    64,
                    111,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Social issue request for social assistance from social media. Location: 63 Kallang Bahru, Level 12.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    72,
                    88,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "One person was taken to hospital for burn injuries and smoke inhalation after a fire broke out at a condominium unit in Jurong East on Saturday afternoon (Dec 18).",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    120,
                    131,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "On the other hand, the nearest hospital, Ng Teng Fong General Hospital, will be a little further at around a 20-minute drive.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    41,
                    70,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Singapore is one-and-a-half degrees north of the equator, lying entirely between the 1st and 2nd parallels.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    9,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Dr Kan Ee May, lecturer at the Nanyang Polytechnic School of Engineering, noted that the centre hopes to help cash-strapped SMEs adopt such solutions, which can cost as little as $1.50 per plant.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    31,
                    50,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    51,
                    72,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Masjid Pusara Aman is situated next to Chua Chu Kang Cemetery.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    18,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    39,
                    61,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "In a new pilot scheme under Project Restore, run by social service agency Lutheran Community Care Services (LCCS), Bukit Merah West NPC will refer neighbours at loggerheads to LCCS for help in finding a resolution.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    74,
                    106,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    108,
                    112,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    115,
                    135,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    176,
                    180,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Among the Victoria School B Division hockey players, Jangra Aditya is considered a late starter, having taken up the sport only three years ago.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    10,
                    25,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "On-campus selection may still need to proceed for a small number of courses, where the selection process cannot be meaningfully replicated remotely. For instance, selections for ITE's Nitec in Nursing and Higher Nitec in Performance Production, as well as Nanyang Polytechnic's Diploma in Oral Health Therapy will be conducted on-campus.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    178,
                    181,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    256,
                    275,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The 57.2 kilometres (35.5 mi) line is the longest on the MRT network (this title will be given to the Cross Island line upon its complete opening by the 2040s), with 35 stations, 8 of which (from Lavender to Tiong Bahru and Changi Airport stations) are underground.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    57,
                    60,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    102,
                    119,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    196,
                    204,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    208,
                    219,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    224,
                    246,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "As a result, the Sentosa Merlion will be demolished from year-end, with its last day of operations on 20 October 2019.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    17,
                    32,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Some Protestant churches have also stopped services at their physical locations temporarily.",
        {
            "entities": []
        }
    ],
    [
        "Based on the initial assessment from the video, the mislabelling incident which occurred at our store at FairPrice Xtra @ Ang Mo Kio Hub is likely caused by human error.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    105,
                    119,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    122,
                    136,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The development will be aligned on a central axis, with The Promontory on the opposite side of the bay, offering a panoramic view of the city skyline.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    56,
                    70,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Singapore Management University researchers have delved into attitudes towards cultivated meat. \"We found that Singapore is more collectivistic and positive towards cultivated meat than the Western country, the United States,\" says Angela Leung, co-author of the research and an associate professor of psychology at SMU. The SMU researchers believe their findings could have important implications for novel food industries' global market strategy.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    31,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    111,
                    120,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    211,
                    224,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    316,
                    319,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    325,
                    328,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Detailed urban planning for Singapore eventually started in the 1950s, with the goal to give Singapore a wider economic role in the Federation of Malaya.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    28,
                    37,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    93,
                    102,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    132,
                    152,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "At Queen's Arc in Queenstown, close to five first-time applicants will be competing for each of the 534 four-room flats, despite the project having the longest wait time of more than five years.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    3,
                    14,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    18,
                    28,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "This area remains the Central Area of Singapore.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    22,
                    34,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    38,
                    47,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The building, which has a gross floor area of 110,000 sq ft, is expected to double the company's research and engineering footprint in Singapore. Dyson employs about 1,400 people in Singapore, and said in April that it will be hiring 250 more engineers and scientists over the next five years as it expands further into areas such as robotics, machine learning and artificial intelligence.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    135,
                    144,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    146,
                    151,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    182,
                    191,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "And a hornbill's stomach was likely the last destination for one such pet bird, as that hornbill attacked and pulled said bird from its cage at Block 115 Bukit Purmei Road in a video sent to Stomp on Monday (Aug 16).",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    144,
                    171,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    191,
                    196,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The new look of Pan Pacific Serviced Suites Orchard - with sky gardens, spacious suites and aqua fitness equipment - was unveiled in April.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    16,
                    51,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Sitting along South Bridge Road, Masjid Jamae is one of the oldest mosques in the city.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    14,
                    31,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    33,
                    45,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "In February, the Goodwood Park Hotel finished its latest round of renovations, which cost $5 million. The decor is contemporary, with clean lines and white quartz. The hotel collects feedback from guests such as Mr Jean Drouffe, the chief executive of AXA Insurance, who recently stayed in a refreshed Poolside Suite with his wife.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    17,
                    36,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    252,
                    265,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Based on the feedback from this focus group, which emphasized strengthening green infrastructure, empowering green practices, and making Singapore an endearing home, the Concept Plan was formed.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    137,
                    146,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Speaking of the Woodlands Health Campus, It's an ambitious project, and is due for opening in 2023.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    16,
                    39,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Mdm Sophia Pang, 51, a Bukit Panjang resident of over 25 years, noted that Dr Teo had enjoyed strong support because of his work in the constituency and rapport with the residents. Dr Samuel Chng, 31, who has lived in the estate since he was born, observed that both PAP and SDP are campaigning harder in this GE, compared with the past two elections that he had been eligible to vote in.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    23,
                    36,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    267,
                    270,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    275,
                    278,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
