[
    [
        "The construction of the North-South Corridor (NSC) has resulted in road diversions around the Novena area.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    24,
                    44,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    46,
                    49,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    94,
                    100,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Launched by Ah Girls Go Army actress Debra Loi, Singapore Crawfish Ramen in Shenton Food Hall claims to be the first crawfish ramen in Singapore. The food hall is located inside Shenton House.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    48,
                    72,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    76,
                    93,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    135,
                    144,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    178,
                    191,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Following Race Course Road and Serangoon Road through Little India and Boon Keng, it cuts through Whampoa River and Kallang River before reaching Potong Pasir.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    10,
                    26,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    31,
                    45,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    54,
                    66,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    71,
                    80,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    98,
                    111,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    116,
                    129,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    146,
                    158,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The stadium (replete with a full 400m track) can also be found nearby, as well as a SAFRA Toa Payoh club.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    84,
                    99,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Phase 1 includes new developments such as the already-completed Outram Community Hospital, SGH Accident & Emergency Block, SGH Elective Care Centre, a new National Dental Centre Singapore (NDCS), and a new National Cancer Centre Singapore (NCCS).",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    64,
                    89,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    91,
                    121,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    123,
                    147,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    155,
                    187,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    189,
                    193,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    206,
                    238,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    240,
                    244,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The Singapore Cable Car is a three-station gondola lift system that plies between Mount Faber on the main island of Singapore and the resort island of Sentosa via HarbourFront.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    4,
                    23,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    82,
                    93,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    116,
                    125,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    151,
                    158,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    163,
                    175,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Will likely be fully integrated with Pasir Ris Park and make this one of the rare BTO projects adjoining a park of this scale.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    37,
                    51,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "In January 1975, the section of the expressway between Jalan Eunos and Kallang Bahru was completed, and Jalan Kolam Bahru, between Kallang Bahru and Woodsville Circus, was improved to form a part of the expressway.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    55,
                    66,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    71,
                    84,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    104,
                    121,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    131,
                    144,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    149,
                    166,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Sungei Kadut MRT station, to be located between Yew Tee MRT station and Kranji MRT station, will serve industries in the area as well as the upcoming Sungei Kadut Eco-District.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    24,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    48,
                    67,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    72,
                    90,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    150,
                    175,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Turn off Hill St onto Coleman St, and you'll be greeted by a string of historic buildings leading up to Fort Canning Park.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    9,
                    16,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    22,
                    32,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    104,
                    121,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "NParks was \"alerted to a snapped trunk of an Angsana tree\" along Lim Chu Kang Road at 7.10pm.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    6,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    65,
                    82,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The section of the expressway between Upper Bukit Timah and Corporation Road was opened soon after on 31 January 1981 by Lee Yiok Seng, the Parliamentary Secretary of National Development at the time.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    38,
                    55,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    60,
                    76,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The North South line forms an incomplete loop from Jurong East in the West Region of Singapore, north to Woodlands and Sembawang, and south to the Central Area.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    4,
                    20,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    51,
                    62,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    85,
                    94,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    70,
                    81,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    105,
                    114,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    119,
                    128,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    147,
                    159,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "A video of the incident circulating on social media showed the man crossing the street towards the police centre at Clementi Ave 5 with what appears to be a knife in his hand while police officers point their firearms at him.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    116,
                    130,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "On 14 October 2020, train services from Jurong East to Woodlands stations were disrupted for more than three and a half hours, owing to a faulty power cable, which affected the East West Line and Circle Line too.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    40,
                    51,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    55,
                    72,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    177,
                    191,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    196,
                    207,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "On 26 April 2005, Today reported that soil tests were being conducted around Chinatown station, raising speculations of a possible rail link between Chinatown and Marina Bay via a new developing downtown.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    18,
                    23,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    77,
                    94,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    149,
                    158,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    163,
                    173,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Intended to connect Singapore's satellite towns and industrial estates, it would act as the main connector between the parts of Singapore and would handle high traffic volumes.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    20,
                    29,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    128,
                    137,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Initially built as a \"shell station\" as part of the Downtown line Phase 2, Hume MRT Station (DT4), located between Beauty World MRT station and Hillview MRT station, will be opened by 2025 when the surrounding areas of Upper Bukit Timah and Hume Avenue are built up with new developments.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    52,
                    65,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    75,
                    91,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    115,
                    139,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    144,
                    164,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    219,
                    236,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    241,
                    252,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "EPS Gantry recently installed at 3 points near my block at 183C Rivervale. But design of gantry is poor, vehicle can still park at the bin centre and loading area to avoid paying charges.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    59,
                    73,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "A two-station extension to Marina Bay opened on 14 January 2012.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    27,
                    37,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "In 2019, about 60m of Fusionopolis Way road in one-north Business Park was converted into a pedestrianised street on a trial basis.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    22,
                    38,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "I have just done the application for a two room flexi. Keeping my fingers crossed as I like Dakota Crescent.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    92,
                    107,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "A criminal inquiry found the main contractor Nishimatsu Construction Company and joint venture partner firm Lum Chang Construction Company and their officers, as well as key Land Transport Authority officers responsible for the collapse at Nicoll Highway MRT Station.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    45,
                    76,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    108,
                    138,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    174,
                    198,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    240,
                    266,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "This was further motivated by the vision that Singapore will play a wider economic role in the Federation of Malaya.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    46,
                    55,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    95,
                    115,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "A new air-conditioned platform to serve southbound trains to Marina South Pier was constructed and opened for service on 27 July 2008.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    61,
                    78,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Romp of otters spotted crossing the road beside The Istana with police officers helping to control the traffic.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    48,
                    58,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "All the trains on the North South Line run with a six-car formation.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    22,
                    38,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Currently under construction, the 42,300 square-metre One Punggol in Punggol will feature a 700-seat hawker centre and the Punggol Regional Library among a variety of other amenities such as the revamped Punggol Vista Community Centre, a childcare centre, and multiple healthcare service centres.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    54,
                    65,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    69,
                    76,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    123,
                    147,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    204,
                    234,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "In addition, with the successful purchase of the site at Tan Quee Lan Street which is located directly above Bugis MRT station and across the Guoco Midtown site, two 30-storey residential towers with more than 500 residential units as well as a public retail podium will be built by GuocoLand.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    57,
                    76,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    109,
                    126,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    142,
                    155,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    283,
                    292,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Singapore has two land links to Malaysia.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    9,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    32,
                    40,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Firefly, a Malaysian operator based at Kuala Lumpur's Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Airport in Subang, operates out of Seletar Airport instead of Changi Airport.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    7,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    39,
                    51,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    54,
                    84,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    88,
                    94,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    112,
                    127,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    139,
                    153,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Previously proposed as an LRT line, the Jurong Region Line was re-proposed into a fully elevated MRT line 24 km long with 24 stations.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    26,
                    29,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    40,
                    58,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    97,
                    100,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Naked man doing indecent acts at playground near Blk 364A Sembawang Crescent photographed by passer-by.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    49,
                    76,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "This has led to disagreements with Malaysia.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    35,
                    43,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "On the other hand, the nearest hospital, Ng Teng Fong General Hospital, will be a little further at around a 20-minute drive.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    41,
                    70,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "In addition, the contractors had to divert the Singapore River for the tunnels' construction.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    47,
                    62,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Lady vaping on MRT train after train left Outram Park station.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    15,
                    18,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    42,
                    61,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The upcoming Founders' Memorial will be located in a 5ha site in Bay East Garden.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    13,
                    31,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    65,
                    80,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Some were hit by vehicle while crossing the highway,I saw once at TPE near Sengkang.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    66,
                    69,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    75,
                    83,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Rising electricity prices have proved to be the last straw for Pin Si Restaurant in Safra Yishun club, after it had been grappling with manpower shortages since the start of the Covid-19 pandemic.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    63,
                    80,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    84,
                    96,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The other station with similar architecture is Dover.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    47,
                    52,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "On weekdays and Saturdays, the first train on the line departs from the northern terminus Punggol at 5.42 am, while the last train on the line departs from the southern terminus HarbourFront at 11:56 pm.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    90,
                    97,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    178,
                    190,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Singapore's main territory is a diamond-shaped island, although its territory includes surrounding smaller islands.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    9,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "A 34-storey commercial development will also be built above the Labrador Underground Substation.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    64,
                    95,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Having first started out as an online store, Breakfast Grill has converted to a brick-and-mortar store at 380 East Coast Road. Nearby neighbourhoods include Telok Kurau and Marine Parade.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    45,
                    60,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    106,
                    125,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    157,
                    168,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    173,
                    186,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Sembawang station and Kranji station were later included in the construction after the second round of planning (construction began at the same time on 19 November 1992) and Sungei Kadut station was then omitted.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    17,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    22,
                    36,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    174,
                    194,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "One of the boards has been retired and will be donated to the National Heritage Board (NHB) to become part of Singapore's National Collection.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    62,
                    85,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    87,
                    90,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    110,
                    119,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The hole, directly in front of two private houses along Cornwall Gardens, measured 8 by 7 metres and was 3 metres deep.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    56,
                    72,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Initially to be located as part of the Thomson-East Coast MRT line Mandai Depot, the RTS link depot will be relocated to Wadi Hana in Johor Bahru instead.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    39,
                    66,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    67,
                    79,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    85,
                    93,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    121,
                    130,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    134,
                    145,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "At Little India station, the metal grills of the station walls have leaf-shaped patterns similar to the door patterns to the Hindu prayer rooms.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    3,
                    23,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Selected trains departing from Marina South Pier station will also terminate at Kranji station in the late evenings.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    31,
                    56,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    80,
                    95,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The 7-metre (23 ft) wide and 3.5-metre (11 ft) deep CUT, located along Pickering Street and Church Street, was constructed using the cut and cover method.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    52,
                    55,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    71,
                    87,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    92,
                    105,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Thus, we predict that it just might be this 3.9 gross plot ratio area beside the upcoming Keat Hong Verge BTO flats.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    90,
                    105,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Senior Minister of State for Health, and Communications and Information, Dr Janil Puthucheary, who is an MP for Pasir Ris-Punggol GRC, said at the topping-up ceremony yesterday that while construction was delayed because of the pandemic, it is on track to open progressively.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    112,
                    133,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Avenue South Residence is a 1074-unit condominium currently being built at Silat Avenue, along the historic KTM Rail Corridor.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    22,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    75,
                    87,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    108,
                    111,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    112,
                    125,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "A malfunction in the platform screen doors at Botanic Gardens station resulted in trains bypassing the station and a seven-hour disruption on 3 May 2017.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    46,
                    69,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The food I bought from economic rice stall at Block 618 Yishun Street 61 caused my mum to have food poisoning.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    46,
                    72,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The line would interchange with the existing MRT system at Dhoby Ghaut station and pass through Kandang Kerbau and Hougang, paralleling the major roads of Serangoon Road and Upper Serangoon Road.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    45,
                    48,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    59,
                    78,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    96,
                    110,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    115,
                    122,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    155,
                    169,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    174,
                    194,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Singapore officially separated from Malaysia on 9 August 1965 and attained independence.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    9,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    36,
                    44,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Other than providing a convenient one-stop centre offering public services, the new centre will also house a number of service centres, a heritage centre, the Registrar of Societies, and the Casino Regulatory Authority.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    159,
                    181,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    191,
                    218,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "By July 2019, the Mean Kilometres Between Failure (MKBF) for the North South and East West lines had jumped to 700,000 km and 1,400,000 km respectively.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    65,
                    76,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    81,
                    95,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "An additional extension to the Downtown Line to Sungei Kadut station from Bukit Panjang station was announced on 25 May 2019 by the LTA.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    31,
                    44,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    48,
                    68,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    74,
                    95,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "It involved multiple diversions of the main roads and the Eu Tong Sen Canal, in addition to the preservation of the Garden Bridge.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    58,
                    75,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    116,
                    129,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Sengkang Depot also hosts the Operations Control Centre (OCC) for the North East Line.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    14,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    30,
                    55,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    57,
                    60,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    70,
                    85,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The new elliptical entrance serving the DTL station reflects the elliptical facade of the nearby Hong Lim Complex.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    40,
                    43,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    97,
                    113,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Partnering the Kampong Gelam Alliance to rejuvenate the Kampong Gelam district with the community.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    15,
                    37,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    56,
                    69,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Located next to the GX-5 Extreme Swing in Clarke Quay and said to be Asia's tallest, Slingshot is an upcoming thrill ride which will catapult riders close to 70 metres into the air, reaching speeds of 160km per hour.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    20,
                    38,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    42,
                    53,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    85,
                    94,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "As a trial run, luggage racks were installed on the C751B trains to serve travellers on the Changi Airport branch line.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    92,
                    118,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "This stall at Hillion Mall did not provide me with a receipt plus HPB QR Code even though I ordered a healthy meal which consisted of Brown Rice and 2 servings of vegetables (long beans and Kai-Lan).",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    14,
                    26,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    66,
                    69,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "However, given that the Government had earlier stated that PLH flats would apply to those in the Greater Southern Waterfront, the city centre as well as the towns surrounding it, to incorporate HDB flats on this Alexandra Road site as part of the scheme will open the dam for a huge number of future public flats to also qualify.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    24,
                    34,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    97,
                    124,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    212,
                    226,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    194,
                    197,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "On 17 January 2013, then-Minister for Transport Lui Tuck Yew announced 'Circle Line Stage 6' which will 'close the circle', set to be completed by 2025.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    72,
                    83,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "At Outram Park station, to minimise any movement to the East West line (EWL) tunnels, an arch roof of steel pipes filled with cement were laid underneath the EWL tunnels.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    3,
                    22,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    56,
                    70,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    72,
                    75,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    158,
                    161,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Folks who know of Tony Cafe, the caifan eatery in The Adelphi, and their wildly popular chicken wings will be happy to know that they can now get their fill of deep-fried chicken wings and honey chicken wings with chicken rice in a canteen in Fragrance Empire Building in Alexandra.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    18,
                    27,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    50,
                    61,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    243,
                    268,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    272,
                    281,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "A community club (Mountbatten CC) will be part of the project, for some It'll be like having your very own clubhouse.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    18,
                    32,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "It is the first MRT line to be built in Singapore, with the first section from Yio Chu Kang station to Toa Payoh station beginning service on 7 November 1987, followed by an extension southwards to Raffles Place station on 12 December the same year and northwards to Yishun station on 20 December 1988.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    16,
                    19,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    40,
                    49,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    79,
                    99,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    103,
                    120,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    198,
                    219,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    267,
                    281,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The line then runs along Hougang Avenue 6 and Sengkang Central to Sengkang station in Sengkang and further extends to Punggol station in Punggol town, where the line terminates.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    25,
                    41,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    46,
                    62,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    66,
                    82,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    86,
                    94,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    118,
                    133,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    137,
                    149,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "According to SMRT, the disruption was caused by damage to the third rail and the trains' collector shoes.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    13,
                    17,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The Mass Rapid Transit Corporation (MRTC) - later renamed SMRT Corporation-was established on 14 October 1983 and took over the roles and responsibilities of the former provisional Mass Rapid Transit Authority.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    4,
                    34,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    36,
                    40,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    58,
                    74,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    181,
                    209,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The strongest one I'm looking at would be at the stretch of Jalan Bukit Merah from Kampong Bahru to Queensway, perhaps extending the line through one-north to the MRT station there, or a short stretch up the rail corridor to Tanglin Halt and Buona Vista, dusting off some of the old Buona Vista LRT plans from the 1990s.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    60,
                    77,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    83,
                    96,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    100,
                    109,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    146,
                    155,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    163,
                    166,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    225,
                    237,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    242,
                    253,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    283,
                    298,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "However, with Singapore's direction of development unclear, the 1965 Plan was held back.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    14,
                    24,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "A new polyclinic in Sembawang is slated to open by this year, while six others in Kaki Bukit, Khatib, Serangoon, Tampines North, Tengah and Yew Tee will open by 2026, according to ST.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    20,
                    29,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    82,
                    92,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    94,
                    100,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    102,
                    111,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    113,
                    127,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    129,
                    135,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    140,
                    147,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    180,
                    182,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "ParkView @ Bidadari is three-minute walk away from the The Woodleigh Mall, which will also house an integrated transport hub with an air-conditioned bus interchange and linkage to Woodleigh MRT station.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    19,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    55,
                    73,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    180,
                    201,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The former Admiralty House will also be restored as part of the plans.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    11,
                    26,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "In Orchard, more mixed-use developments will be constructed on empty plots of land along Orchard Boulevard above Orchard MRT station.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    3,
                    10,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    89,
                    106,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    113,
                    132,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Changi Northern and Southern CorridorA two-part infrastructure project near Changi Airport designed to complement the upcoming Cross Island MRT line and future Changi Airport Terminal 5, the Changi Northern and Southern Corridor includes the widening of existing roads, building of new roads, a new viaduct, and erecting new cycling paths.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    37,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    76,
                    90,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    191,
                    228,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    160,
                    185,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    127,
                    148,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Stage 3, the final stage of the Downtown Line, opened on 21 October 2017 with its official opening made on 20 October 2017 by Coordinating Minister for Infrastructure and Minister for Transport Khaw Boon Wan.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    32,
                    45,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "They are selling Hottis snacks at 224A Punggol.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    34,
                    46,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "With the exception of Bishan, Braddell and Canberra stations, the other stations have island platforms.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    22,
                    28,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    30,
                    38,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    43,
                    59,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Construction from Jalan Anak Bukit to Boon Lay Road was started in 1978.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    18,
                    34,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    38,
                    51,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The 42-kilometre (26 mi), 34 station fully underground Downtown Line connects the north-west and eastern regions of Singapore with a loop travelling through the city center.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    55,
                    68,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    116,
                    125,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Initially built as a temporary National Day Parade (NDP) venue while the new National Stadium was under construction, The Float @ Marina Bay can seat 27,000 spectators and has hosted the event nine times since 2007, most recently in 2018.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    118,
                    140,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The Bukit Timah Line aimed to alleviate the traffic problems along the Bukit Timah and Dunearn Road corridor, and provide a direct link to the city area for residents in Choa Chu Kang and Bukit Panjang.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    4,
                    20,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    170,
                    183,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    188,
                    201,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    71,
                    82,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    87,
                    99,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The estate will also house a mixed-use development named The Woodleigh Residences and The Woodleigh Mall.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    57,
                    81,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    86,
                    104,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The extension has a span of 7.5 kilometres (4.7 mi), which spans a twin-tracked MRT viaduct, four above-ground stations and a 26-hectare depot to provide stabling and maintenance facilities for the additional trains that will be bought for the extension and to cater for future expansion of the line.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    80,
                    83,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Until everything eventually comes together in the 2030s, residents of the Tampines North BTO plots can just hop across to IKEA, Giant and Courts whenever they wish.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    74,
                    88,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    122,
                    126,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    128,
                    133,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    138,
                    144,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "At 41.9 kilometres (26.0 mi), the DTL is the longest underground and automated rapid transit line in Singapore as of 2017.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    34,
                    37,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    101,
                    110,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Unknown red Mitsubishi car failed to conform to traffic red light signal and almost hit 2 pedestrians and a biker at the junction of Queensway and Commonwealth Drive.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    12,
                    22,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    133,
                    142,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    147,
                    165,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The 57.2 kilometres (35.5 mi) line is the longest on the MRT network (this title will be given to the Cross Island line upon its complete opening by the 2040s), with 35 stations, 8 of which (from Lavender to Tiong Bahru and Changi Airport stations) are underground.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    57,
                    60,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    102,
                    119,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    196,
                    204,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    208,
                    219,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    224,
                    246,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The five-level underground station is also integrated with the twin-towered office complex Atrium@Orchard above the station.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    91,
                    105,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "38 people, which include two SMRT staff were hospitalized.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    29,
                    33,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Get well acquainted with Singapore's arts scene at Aliwal Arts Centre.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    25,
                    34,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    51,
                    69,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The bowls in foodcourt in Causeway Point and Vista Point are very dirty with rice and meehoon and other stains.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    26,
                    40,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    45,
                    56,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "On 13 October 2021, Mandai Wildlife Group introduced a rebranding of the five parks, unveiling new logos and the renaming of River Safari and Jurong Bird Park to River Wonders and Bird Paradise, respectively.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    20,
                    41,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    125,
                    137,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    142,
                    158,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    162,
                    175,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    180,
                    193,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "As part of Phase 6 of the buildout of Biopolis, Elementum building is set to be completed by mid-2022.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    38,
                    46,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    48,
                    57,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Numerous changes were made to the number of stations for the extension mainly to accommodate the 1991 Concept Plan by the Urban Redevelopment Authority, which aimed to make Woodlands a regional centre for northern Singapore.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    122,
                    151,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    173,
                    182,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    214,
                    223,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Tomlinson Heights is located near Singapore's prime shopping district Orchard Road and is close to many lifestyle and entertainment options as well as several schools. It is within convenient walking distance to Orchard MRT station and the upcoming Orchard Boulevard MRT.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    17,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    34,
                    43,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    70,
                    82,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    212,
                    231,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    249,
                    270,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Announced on 25 June 2019, a second Raffles Hotel named Raffles Sentosa Resort & Spa Singapore will be built on Sentosa at the site adjacent to the existing Sofitel Singapore Sentosa Resort & Spa.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    36,
                    49,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    56,
                    94,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    112,
                    119,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    157,
                    195,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "SMRT said that a tree branch fell on one of its service 975 revenue buses at about 4.25pm.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    4,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "When Singapore was first colonized by the British, the City of Singapore was situated on the southern coast, around the mouth of the Singapore River.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    5,
                    14,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    63,
                    72,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    133,
                    148,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Bishan Community Centre has study rooms as well.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    23,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Masjid Pusara Aman is situated next to Chua Chu Kang Cemetery.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    18,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    39,
                    61,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The North South line runs parallel to the East West line at the City Hall and Raffles Place stations, which are also cross-platform interchanges to the East West line.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    4,
                    20,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    42,
                    56,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    64,
                    73,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    78,
                    99,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    152,
                    166,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Buses were temporarily diverted along Lorong Rusuk towards Lim Chu Kang Road.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    38,
                    50,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    59,
                    76,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The last stage of the line from Harbourfront to Marina Bay will be completed in 2026, completing the loop.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    32,
                    44,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    48,
                    58,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "It is the second Mass Rapid Transit line to be built in Singapore.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    17,
                    35,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    56,
                    65,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Your best bet would be Lim Chu Kang cemetery, as there are no local lights for almost a kilometre around.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    23,
                    44,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Many parts of Singapore, including islands such as Sentosa and Jurong Island are accessible by road.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    14,
                    23,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    51,
                    58,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    63,
                    76,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Plantation, the first district out of five, was unveiled on 4 September 2018.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    10,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "During initial stages after opening, the westbound trains will alternate their terminus between Joo Koon and Tuas Link, where for every two trains, one train will terminate at the former, while the other train will terminate at the latter.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    96,
                    104,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    109,
                    118,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "In the 1990s, the line extended to the north and west connecting to the Branch line via Woodlands through the Woodlands line extension.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    88,
                    97,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    110,
                    134,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    72,
                    83,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Singapore is the first country in Southeast Asia to levy a carbon tax, at $5 per ton, applicable for its largest carbon-emitting corporations that produce more than 25,000 tons of carbon dioxide per year.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    9,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    34,
                    48,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Operations of the North South Line are affected by the COVID-19 pandemic, leading to the drop of ridership.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    18,
                    34,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The most recent plan is the 2019 masterplan, which details Singapore's increasing consideration towards sustainability, cultural preservation, building communities and closing resource loops.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    59,
                    68,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "The old signalling system then ceased operations on 2 January 2019.Platform screen doorsWhen the line was first opened, full-height platform screen doors supplied by Westinghouse were installed at underground stations.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    166,
                    178,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Subsequently, installation began in May 2011 at Ang Mo Kio station.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    48,
                    66,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Since 2014, train services on the line have ended earlier for critical maintenance works, with the exception of a break between September 2016 and December 2017.Trains on the NSL are powered via a third rail.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    175,
                    178,
                    "FAC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "On 15 November 2017, at 8:20 am, two trains collided at Joo Koon station, injuring 36 passengers and 2 SMRT staff.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    56,
                    72,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Residents can also go for a jog at the nearby Yishun Pond.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    46,
                    57,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Over 90% of Singaporeans or Permanent Residents own their own home and at the 2010 Venice Architecture Biennale, it was calculated that with Singapore's land-use efficiency, the world's population could fit into 0.5% of the Earth's landmass.",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    83,
                    89,
                    "LOC"
                ],
                [
                    141,
                    150,
                    "LOC"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
