{"id": 25539, "data": "Coloured red on the rail map, the line is 45 kilometres (28 mi) long and serves 27 stations, 11 of which, between the Bishan and Marina South Pier stations, are underground.", "label": [[118, 124, "LOC"], [129, 154, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25540, "data": "It runs from Jurong East station, located in Western Singapore, to Marina South Pier station in the Central Area, via Woodlands station in northern Singapore.", "label": [[13, 32, "LOC"], [45, 62, "LOC"], [67, 92, "LOC"], [100, 112, "LOC"], [118, 135, "LOC"], [148, 157, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25542, "data": "All the trains on the North South Line run with a six-car formation.", "label": [[22, 38, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25543, "data": "It is the first MRT line to be built in Singapore, with the first section from Yio Chu Kang station to Toa Payoh station beginning service on 7 November 1987, followed by an extension southwards to Raffles Place station on 12 December the same year and northwards to Yishun station on 20 December 1988.", "label": [[16, 19, "FAC"], [40, 49, "LOC"], [79, 99, "LOC"], [103, 120, "LOC"], [198, 219, "LOC"], [267, 281, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25544, "data": "After the southern extension to Marina Bay station opened on 4 November 1989, the North South line was formed and split from the East West line.", "label": [[32, 50, "LOC"], [82, 98, "FAC"], [129, 143, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25545, "data": "In the 1990s, the line extended to the north and west connecting to the Branch line via Woodlands through the Woodlands line extension.", "label": [[88, 97, "LOC"], [110, 134, "FAC"], [72, 83, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25546, "data": "Since the 2010s, due to the ageing infrastructure of the North South Line (being the oldest and heavily utilised MRT line), significant improvements have been made on this line, such as the replacement of sleepers, third rail replacement and the introduction of new rolling stocks (the C151B and the C151C) to replace the older rolling stocks and increase passenger capacity.", "label": [[57, 73, "FAC"], [113, 116, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25547, "data": "The North South Line is also the first line to have undergone a major re-signalling project, converting it from semi-automatic to fully automated operations in 2019.", "label": [[4, 20, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25548, "data": "Other recent developments of the line include a new extension to Marina South Pier station on 23 November 2014 and a new infill station, Canberra station, on 2 November 2019.", "label": [[65, 90, "LOC"], [137, 153, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25550, "data": "HistoryInitial developmentsThe Mass Rapid Transit (MRT) originated from a forecast in 1967 by the planners of the State and City Planning Project, which stated the need for a rail-based urban transport system in Singapore by 1992.", "label": [[31, 49, "FAC"], [51, 54, "FAC"], [212, 221, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25552, "data": "After deciding on a rail-based system, the construction of Phase I of the MRT system, which will be the North South line, was given priority as the line passes through areas having a higher demand for public transport, such as the densely populated housing estates of Toa Payoh and Ang Mo Kio and the Central Area.", "label": [[74, 77, "FAC"], [268, 277, "LOC"], [282, 292, "LOC"], [301, 313, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25553, "data": "The line was expected to relieve the traffic congestion on the Thomson-Sembawang road corridor.", "label": [[63, 70, "LOC"], [71, 80, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25554, "data": "Construction of the MRT line (and also the MRT system itself) started on 22 October 1983, and the first section from Yio Chu Kang station to Toa Payoh station opened on 7 November 1987.", "label": [[20, 23, "FAC"], [43, 46, "FAC"], [117, 137, "LOC"], [141, 158, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25556, "data": "Dr Yeo Ning Hong, the Minister For Communications and Information, inaugurated the start of MRT operations and announced it to be the \"beginning\" of the MRT system.", "label": [[92, 95, "FAC"], [153, 156, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25557, "data": "Nine more stations from Novena station to Outram Park station via Raffles Place opened on 12 December that year and it began independent operations on 4 November 1989 as the North South line when the extension to Marina Bay station was opened.", "label": [[24, 38, "LOC"], [42, 61, "LOC"], [66, 79, "LOC"], [174, 190, "FAC"], [213, 231, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25558, "data": "After the Branch line (from the Jurong East to Choa Chu Kang stations) opened in 1990, the Woodlands MRT line was envisioned so as to close the gap between Yishun and Choa Chu Kang stations.", "label": [[10, 21, "FAC"], [32, 43, "LOC"], [47, 68, "LOC"], [91, 109, "FAC"], [156, 162, "LOC"], [167, 188, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25559, "data": "Numerous changes were made to the number of stations for the extension mainly to accommodate the 1991 Concept Plan by the Urban Redevelopment Authority, which aimed to make Woodlands a regional centre for northern Singapore.", "label": [[122, 151, "ORG"], [173, 182, "LOC"], [214, 223, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25561, "data": "Sembawang station and Kranji station were later included in the construction after the second round of planning (construction began at the same time on 19 November 1992) and Sungei Kadut station was then omitted.", "label": [[0, 17, "LOC"], [22, 36, "LOC"], [174, 194, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25562, "data": "Sungei Kadut will be built later if the town's population justifies the necessity for the station.", "label": [[0, 12, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25564, "data": "There was also a need to level the land covered in thick vegetation in Kadut, Woodlands and Sembawang for the MRT line.", "label": [[71, 76, "LOC"], [78, 87, "LOC"], [92, 101, "LOC"], [110, 113, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25567, "data": "Subsequent developmentsThe NSL platforms of the Bishan station underwent major alterations to increase the passenger capacity of the station from 1,250 to 2,020.", "label": [[27, 30, "FAC"], [48, 62, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25568, "data": "A new air-conditioned platform to serve southbound trains to Marina South Pier was constructed and opened for service on 27 July 2008.", "label": [[61, 78, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25576, "data": "In the 2008 Land Transport Master Plan, the 1-kilometre (0.6 mi) North South Line extension was announced as one of the upcoming projects rolled out by the Land Transport Authority to expand Singapore's rail network.", "label": [[65, 91, "FAC"], [156, 180, "ORG"], [191, 200, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25578, "data": "This extension serves the Marina South Pier, the Marina Bay Cruise Centre Singapore, and future developments in the Marina Bay Downtown area.", "label": [[26, 43, "LOC"], [49, 83, "LOC"], [116, 126, "LOC"], [127, 135, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25580, "data": "The feasibility study was completed in 2014 and LTA announced Canberra as a new station.", "label": [[48, 51, "LOC"], [62, 70, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25581, "data": "Construction of Canberra station commenced on 26 March 2016.", "label": [[16, 32, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25582, "data": "The station, which is an infill station with side platforms, was built along an operational section of the line between Sembawang and Yishun.", "label": [[120, 129, "LOC"], [134, 140, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25583, "data": "Canberra station opened on 2 November 2019.", "label": [[0, 16, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25586, "data": "The accident disrupted train services for more than three hours and cost SMRT between S$100,000 and $150,000 in damages and lost revenue.", "label": [[73, 77, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 25587, "data": "On 15 December 2011, train services between Bishan and Marina Bay stations were disrupted due to damage sustained on the power rail between City Hall and Dhoby Ghaut.", "label": [[44, 50, "LOC"], [55, 73, "LOC"], [140, 149, "LOC"], [154, 165, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25590, "data": "According to SMRT, the disruption was caused by damage to the third rail and the trains' collector shoes.", "label": [[13, 17, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 25593, "data": "For this disruption that brought inconvenience to 413,000 commuters, LTA imposed a 'record' fine of S$5.4 million on SMRT.On 7 October 2017, a 20-hour long disruption of services started due to flooding in the tunnels between Braddell station and Bishan station due to a faulty drainage system, resulting in disruption of train services between Ang Mo Kio and Marina South Pier stations in both directions for several hours.", "label": [[69, 72, "ORG"], [117, 121, "ORG"], [247, 261, "LOC"], [226, 242, "LOC"], [345, 355, "LOC"], [360, 385, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25594, "data": "A trackside fire between Raffles Place and Marina Bay stations further exacerbated the disruption.", "label": [[25, 38, "LOC"], [43, 61, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25595, "data": "Train services between Marina South Pier and Newton resumed at about 9:20 pm on the same day, followed by Newton and Ang Mo Kio at around 2 pm the following day.", "label": [[23, 40, "LOC"], [45, 51, "LOC"], [106, 112, "LOC"], [117, 127, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25597, "data": "On 14 October 2020, train services from Jurong East to Woodlands stations were disrupted for more than three and a half hours, owing to a faulty power cable, which affected the East West Line and Circle Line too.", "label": [[40, 51, "LOC"], [55, 72, "LOC"], [177, 191, "FAC"], [196, 207, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25600, "data": "Service resumed at all stations along the north-south and East-West Lines at 10:35 pm.", "label": [[42, 53, "FAC"], [58, 72, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25604, "data": "Network and operationsServicesTrain services on the North South MRT line operates from approximately 5:30 am to around midnight daily.", "label": [[52, 72, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25608, "data": "In the evenings, selected trains from Jurong East station will terminate at the Ang Mo Kio and Toa Payoh stations.", "label": [[38, 57, "LOC"], [80, 90, "LOC"], [95, 112, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25609, "data": "Selected trains departing from Marina South Pier station will also terminate at Kranji station in the late evenings.", "label": [[31, 56, "LOC"], [80, 95, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25610, "data": "Train services on the North South Line are also subjected to maintenance and renewal works, usually on selected Fridays & Saturdays.", "label": [[22, 38, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25611, "data": "Operations of the North South Line are affected by the COVID-19 pandemic, leading to the drop of ridership.", "label": [[18, 34, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25612, "data": "The North South line forms an incomplete loop from Jurong East in the West Region of Singapore, north to Woodlands and Sembawang, and south to the Central Area.", "label": [[4, 20, "FAC"], [51, 62, "LOC"], [85, 94, "LOC"], [70, 81, "LOC"], [105, 114, "LOC"], [119, 128, "LOC"], [147, 159, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25613, "data": "It is 45 kilometres (28 mi) long and is predominantly double-tracked, but certain short sections at the Woodlands, Yishun and Ang Mo Kio stations widen to three tracks, and four tracks at Jurong East station.", "label": [[104, 113, "LOC"], [115, 121, "LOC"], [126, 144, "LOC"], [188, 207, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25616, "data": "After Sembawang station, the line follows the route of Canberra Link and Yishun Avenue 2, curving southwards.", "label": [[6, 23, "LOC"], [55, 68, "LOC"], [73, 88, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25618, "data": "The line continues above ground for the Yio Chu Kang and Ang Mo Kio stations, then it goes back to surface level for Bishan station, the MRT system's only at-grade station.", "label": [[40, 52, "LOC"], [57, 75, "LOC"], [117, 131, "LOC"], [137, 140, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25621, "data": "The North South line runs parallel to the East West line at the City Hall and Raffles Place stations, which are also cross-platform interchanges to the East West line.", "label": [[4, 20, "FAC"], [42, 56, "FAC"], [64, 73, "LOC"], [78, 99, "LOC"], [152, 166, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25622, "data": "The line terminates at Marina South Pier.", "label": [[23, 40, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25625, "data": "With the exception of Bishan, Braddell and Canberra stations, the other stations have island platforms.", "label": [[22, 28, "LOC"], [30, 38, "LOC"], [43, 59, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25634, "data": "The C151C trains is also the first MRT rolling stock on the NSEWL to be fitted with tip-up seats, in addition to the current features of the C151B trains.", "label": [[35, 38, "FAC"], [60, 65, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25638, "data": "However, the ageing system had undermined the rail reliability on the line, requiring the NSL to upgrade its signalling system.", "label": [[90, 93, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25648, "data": "Since 28 May 2017, the new signalling system has been operating full-day on the North South line.", "label": [[80, 96, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25649, "data": "The old signalling system then ceased operations on 2 January 2019.Platform screen doorsWhen the line was first opened, full-height platform screen doors supplied by Westinghouse were installed at underground stations.", "label": [[166, 178, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 25654, "data": "Subsequently, installation began in May 2011 at Ang Mo Kio station.", "label": [[48, 66, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25658, "data": "Since 2014, train services on the line have ended earlier for critical maintenance works, with the exception of a break between September 2016 and December 2017.Trains on the NSL are powered via a third rail.", "label": [[175, 178, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25662, "data": "The East West line (EWL) is a high-capacity Mass Rapid Transit (MRT) line operated by SMRT, running from Pasir Ris station in the east to Tuas Link station in the west, with an additional branch between Changi Airport and Tanah Merah stations.", "label": [[4, 18, "FAC"], [20, 23, "FAC"], [44, 62, "FAC"], [64, 67, "FAC"], [86, 90, "ORG"], [105, 122, "LOC"], [138, 155, "LOC"], [203, 217, "LOC"], [222, 241, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25663, "data": "It is the second Mass Rapid Transit line to be built in Singapore.", "label": [[17, 35, "FAC"], [56, 65, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25664, "data": "The 57.2 kilometres (35.5 mi) line is the longest on the MRT network (this title will be given to the Cross Island line upon its complete opening by the 2040s), with 35 stations, 8 of which (from Lavender to Tiong Bahru and Changi Airport stations) are underground.", "label": [[57, 60, "FAC"], [102, 119, "FAC"], [196, 204, "LOC"], [208, 219, "LOC"], [224, 246, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25666, "data": "The East West Line signalling systems have been upgraded along with the North South Line and is the second line to have its signalling upgraded completely, converting it from semi-automatic to fully automated operations.", "label": [[4, 18, "FAC"], [72, 88, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25669, "data": "During the construction of the extension to Clementi station, Commonwealth Avenue West was realigned to accommodate the viaduct.", "label": [[44, 60, "LOC"], [62, 86, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25670, "data": "The line was later extended to Lakeside on 5 November 1988.", "label": [[31, 39, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25672, "data": "At that point, the East West line was formed, reflecting the operational split from the North South line which has at the same time extended to Marina Bay station, and uses a green coloured theme.", "label": [[19, 33, "FAC"], [88, 104, "FAC"], [144, 162, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25674, "data": "Boon Lay station opened on 6 July 1990, marking the completion of the initial MRT system.", "label": [[0, 16, "LOC"], [78, 81, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25675, "data": "Construction on a new infill station Dover station between Buona Vista station and Clementi station began in June 1998.", "label": [[37, 50, "LOC"], [59, 78, "LOC"], [83, 99, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25678, "data": "On 18 October 2001, Dover was opened.", "label": [[20, 25, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25680, "data": "Dover is the first station in the MRT network to be built as an infill station.", "label": [[0, 5, "LOC"], [34, 37, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25681, "data": "The idea of extending the Mass Rapid Transit system to Changi Airport was reconsidered when Terminal 3 of the airport was being built.", "label": [[26, 44, "FAC"], [55, 69, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25689, "data": "On 25 May 2019, it was announced that the Changi Airport Extension will be converted to become part of Thomson-East Coast line Extension (TELe) by 2040.Boon Lay and Tuas extensionThe 3.8-kilometre (2.4 mi) Boon Lay extension was first announced by the LTA on 29 December 2004, set to serve residents from the Jurong West Town area and those working in the Jurong Industrial Estate.", "label": [[42, 66, "FAC"], [103, 136, "FAC"], [138, 142, "FAC"], [152, 179, "FAC"], [206, 224, "FAC"], [252, 255, "ORG"], [309, 320, "LOC"], [356, 380, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25690, "data": "The two stations, Pioneer and Joo Koon stations, officially opened on 28 February 2009.On 11 January 2011, the Tuas West extension, an extension of the East West line from Joo Koon to Tuas Link was announced.", "label": [[18, 25, "LOC"], [30, 46, "LOC"], [111, 130, "FAC"], [152, 166, "FAC"], [172, 180, "LOC"], [184, 193, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25691, "data": "The extension has a span of 7.5 kilometres (4.7 mi), which spans a twin-tracked MRT viaduct, four above-ground stations and a 26-hectare depot to provide stabling and maintenance facilities for the additional trains that will be bought for the extension and to cater for future expansion of the line.", "label": [[80, 83, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25693, "data": "The stations are Gul Circle, Tuas Crescent, Tuas West Road, and Tuas Link.", "label": [[17, 27, "LOC"], [29, 42, "LOC"], [44, 58, "LOC"], [64, 73, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25696, "data": "During initial stages after opening, the westbound trains will alternate their terminus between Joo Koon and Tuas Link, where for every two trains, one train will terminate at the former, while the other train will terminate at the latter.", "label": [[96, 104, "LOC"], [109, 118, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25697, "data": "Additional platform at Tanah Merah station.", "label": [[23, 42, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25701, "data": "When completed in 2024, it will be the second station to have triple island platforms after Jurong East.", "label": [[92, 103, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25702, "data": "The authorities initially rejected the proposal by casting doubts over functionality and concerns about the high installation costs, but made an about-turn later with the government announcing plans to install half-height platform screen doors on the elevated stations on 25 January 2008, citing lower costs due to its becoming a more common feature worldwide.", "label": [[171, 181, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 25707, "data": "The new system became operational between Pioneer and Tuas Link stations on 18 June 2017.", "label": [[42, 49, "LOC"], [54, 71, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25711, "data": "During the evening peak hours on 7 July 2015, train services on the East West and North South lines were temporarily disrupted due to massive power trips detected along both lines.", "label": [[68, 77, "FAC"], [82, 98, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25712, "data": "For this disruption that brought inconvenience to 413,000 commuters, LTA imposed a 'record' fine of S$5.4 million on SMRT.", "label": [[69, 72, "ORG"], [117, 121, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 25714, "data": "In a report, the two trainee staff joined SMRT in January 2016 and worked as technicians under a technical team of 15 staff led by a supervisor and were tasked to go down to the tracks to investigate an alarm triggered by a possible signalling equipment fault close by the station.", "label": [[42, 46, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 25715, "data": "An operator cited that they were granted access to the tracks, but did not coordinate with a Signal Unit in the station to ensure trains could not travel in the area where the team was.", "label": [[93, 104, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25716, "data": "A second train collision occurred on 15 November 2017 at approximately 8.18am, where two C151A trains collided at Joo Koon MRT station.", "label": [[114, 134, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25718, "data": "38 people, which include two SMRT staff were hospitalized.", "label": [[29, 33, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 25719, "data": "Train services between Tuas Link and Joo Koon stations were temporally suspended on both directions for two hours on the day itself and the entire day on 16 November 2017, resulting that the westbound trains would temporarily terminate at Joo Koon.", "label": [[23, 32, "LOC"], [37, 53, "LOC"], [239, 247, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25720, "data": "An update by the Land Transport Authority (LTA) & SMRT on 16 November 2017 stated that LTA and SMRT have decided to isolate for up to one month the operations of the Tuas West extension, which runs on the new signalling system, from the rest of the East West line, which runs on the old signalling system, enabling LTA engineers to carry out further assurance checks together with Thales.", "label": [[17, 41, "ORG"], [43, 46, "ORG"], [50, 54, "ORG"], [87, 90, "ORG"], [95, 99, "ORG"], [166, 185, "FAC"], [249, 263, "FAC"], [315, 318, "ORG"], [381, 387, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 25724, "data": "As its name implies, the East West line connects central Singapore to both eastern and western parts of the island, with an additional branch between Changi Airport and Tanah Merah, which operates as a separate shuttle service.", "label": [[25, 39, "FAC"], [150, 164, "LOC"], [169, 180, "LOC"], [57, 66, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25726, "data": "The line runs mostly on overhead viaducts but goes underground in the city area between Kallang and Redhill, Bedok and Kembangan, and between Expo and Changi Airport.", "label": [[88, 95, "LOC"], [100, 107, "LOC"], [109, 114, "LOC"], [119, 128, "LOC"], [142, 146, "LOC"], [151, 165, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25727, "data": "The line serves 35 stations across 56.7 kilometres (35.2 mi) of track, and station codes for the line are green, corresponding to the line's colour on the system map. 8 stations, Changi Airport and 7 stations on the stretch from Lavender to Tiong Bahru are underground, with the rest being elevated.", "label": [[179, 193, "LOC"], [229, 237, "LOC"], [241, 252, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25730, "data": "By 2040, the Changi Airport line (CAL) will be converted to the Thomson-East Coast line.", "label": [[13, 32, "FAC"], [34, 37, "FAC"], [64, 87, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25732, "data": "These models of rolling stock were introduced to boost the capacity on both the North South and the East West lines in order to cope with increasing ridership.", "label": [[80, 91, "FAC"], [100, 114, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25734, "data": "The C151B trains, which was introduced in April 2017, did not begin revenue service on the full-stretch of the East West Line until the line's trial of the CBTC signalling system in May 2018.", "label": [[111, 125, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25739, "data": "Eastbound trains towards Pasir Ris would have to change back to the old signalling system at Pioneer MRT station.", "label": [[25, 34, "LOC"], [93, 112, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25740, "data": "This procedure was removed after the train collision at Joo Koon as trains terminated at Joo Koon.", "label": [[56, 64, "LOC"], [89, 97, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25741, "data": "Tuas West extension stations have had half-height platform screen doors, manufactured by Fangda, since their opening.", "label": [[0, 19, "FAC"], [89, 95, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 25743, "data": "It runs from Bukit Panjang station in the north-west to Expo station in the east via the Central Area.", "label": [[13, 34, "LOC"], [56, 68, "LOC"], [89, 101, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25744, "data": "The DTL is the fifth MRT line on the network to be opened and the third line to be entirely underground.", "label": [[4, 7, "FAC"], [21, 24, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25746, "data": "Originally planned as three separate lines, the lines merged into the Downtown Line in 2007 and construction began in three stages.", "label": [[70, 83, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25748, "data": "The third and final stage, from Fort Canning to Expo station, opened in October 2017.", "label": [[32, 44, "LOC"], [48, 60, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25749, "data": "At 41.9 kilometres (26.0 mi), the DTL is the longest underground and automated rapid transit line in Singapore as of 2017.", "label": [[34, 37, "FAC"], [101, 110, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25750, "data": "Stage 3e, an extension of the line to Sungei Bedok, is under construction and is scheduled to begin operations in 2024, while a new infill station, Hume station, is planned to open in 2025.", "label": [[38, 50, "LOC"], [148, 160, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25753, "data": "The Bukit Timah Line aimed to alleviate the traffic problems along the Bukit Timah and Dunearn Road corridor, and provide a direct link to the city area for residents in Choa Chu Kang and Bukit Panjang.", "label": [[4, 20, "FAC"], [170, 183, "LOC"], [188, 201, "LOC"], [71, 82, "LOC"], [87, 99, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25757, "data": "On 27 April 2007, then Transport Minister Raymond Lim announced that the Downtown Line would be built in three stages stretching 40 kilometres (25 mi) with 33 stations.", "label": [[73, 86, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25758, "data": "Stage 2, first conceptualized and announced as the Bukit Timah line on 23 October 2001, is 16.6 kilometres (10.3 mi) long with 12 stations connecting Bukit Panjang and Rochor stations, including four interchange stations.", "label": [[51, 67, "FAC"], [150, 163, "LOC"], [168, 183, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25760, "data": "Stage 3 goes from Chinatown to Expo.", "label": [[18, 27, "LOC"], [31, 35, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25761, "data": "The cost exceeded those of the Circle Line (at $6.7 billion) and the North East Line (at $4.6 billion).", "label": [[31, 42, "FAC"], [69, 84, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25764, "data": "The DTL 3 started operations on 21 October 2017, officially opened by Transport Minister Khaw Boon Wan.", "label": [[4, 7, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25765, "data": "To serve the line, the Gali Batu Depot was opened in December 2015 to stable 42 trains.", "label": [[23, 38, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25766, "data": "It is situated at part of the former Kwong Hou Sua Teochew Cemetery off Woodlands Road.", "label": [[37, 67, "LOC"], [72, 86, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25767, "data": "Also in February that year, the Land Transport Authority announced that the capacity of the depot will be expanded to stable 81 trains by 2019.", "label": [[32, 56, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 25768, "data": "On 17 January 2013, plans were announced for a southern extension extending from Expo to connect with the Eastern Region line (ERL); the ERL has since been subsumed into the Thomson-East Coast line.", "label": [[81, 85, "LOC"], [106, 125, "FAC"], [127, 130, "FAC"], [137, 140, "FAC"], [174, 197, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25769, "data": "The extension was to provide more travel options and enhance connectivity for the residents along the East Coast.", "label": [[102, 112, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25770, "data": "The Downtown Line 3 extension (DTL3e) was finalised and announced on 15 August 2014, in conjunction with the announcement of the Thomson-East Coast line.", "label": [[4, 17, "FAC"], [31, 34, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25771, "data": "Two stations, Xilin MRT station and Sungei Bedok MRT station, will be added to the Downtown Line, with Sungei Bedok as an interchange station with the Thomson-East Coast line.", "label": [[14, 31, "LOC"], [36, 60, "LOC"], [83, 96, "FAC"], [103, 115, "LOC"], [151, 174, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25774, "data": "On 7 March 2019, Hume station was announced to be opened by 2025 to better serve Hillview residents.", "label": [[81, 89, "LOC"], [17, 29, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25775, "data": "An additional extension to the Downtown Line to Sungei Kadut station from Bukit Panjang station was announced on 25 May 2019 by the LTA.", "label": [[31, 44, "LOC"], [48, 68, "LOC"], [74, 95, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25777, "data": "A study will also be conducted to determine the stops to be added between the Sungei Kadut and the existing Bukit Panjang stations.", "label": [[78, 90, "LOC"], [108, 129, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25778, "data": "A malfunction in the platform screen doors at Botanic Gardens station resulted in trains bypassing the station and a seven-hour disruption on 3 May 2017.", "label": [[46, 69, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25782, "data": "Before Bukit Panjang station, there exists a brief northwards extension to the line's depot Gali Batu Depot.", "label": [[7, 28, "LOC"], [92, 107, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25783, "data": "The line begins at the Bukit Panjang station and then goes in the southeast direction, running parallel to Upper Bukit Timah Road and along the Bukit Timah Canal through Bukit Timah.", "label": [[23, 44, "LOC"], [107, 129, "LOC"], [144, 161, "LOC"], [170, 181, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25785, "data": "The Downtown line runs parallel to the Circle line at the Promenade and Bayfront stations.", "label": [[4, 17, "FAC"], [39, 50, "FAC"], [58, 67, "LOC"], [72, 88, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25786, "data": "Passing through the Downtown Core, the line interchanges with the North East line at Chinatown station.", "label": [[20, 33, "LOC"], [66, 81, "FAC"], [85, 102, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25788, "data": "Between the Bencoolen and Jalan Besar stations, the line intersects itself, the first MRT line to do so.", "label": [[12, 21, "LOC"], [26, 46, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25789, "data": "After Geylang Bahru station, the line continues in a general eastwards direction, through the industrial areas of Kampong Ubi and Kaki Bukit (briefly paralleling Ubi Avenue 2 and Kaki Bukit Avenue 1), before continuing towards the Tampines Regional Centre and goes southwards, ending at Changi Business Park.", "label": [[6, 27, "LOC"], [114, 125, "LOC"], [130, 140, "LOC"], [162, 174, "LOC"], [179, 198, "LOC"], [231, 255, "LOC"], [287, 307, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25790, "data": "The DTL3 extension (DTL3e) from Expo station will extend the line further towards the Thomson-East Coast line at Sungei Bedok station.", "label": [[4, 7, "FAC"], [20, 23, "FAC"], [32, 44, "LOC"], [86, 109, "FAC"], [113, 133, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25791, "data": "As of 2011, the Downtown line has one type of rolling stock, the Bombardier MOVIA C951(A) cars, running in a three-car formation.", "label": [[16, 29, "FAC"], [65, 75, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 25793, "data": "For the period between the opening of Stage 1 and that of Stage 2, trains were stabled at a maintenance facility that was built at Marina Bay as part of the Circle line project.", "label": [[131, 141, "LOC"], [157, 168, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25795, "data": "On 12 October 2012, the first of 11 trains for the line arrived at Jurong Port.", "label": [[67, 78, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25796, "data": "It was transported to Kim Chuan Depot to undergo testing by the LTA before it was handed over to SBS Transit.", "label": [[22, 37, "LOC"], [64, 67, "ORG"], [97, 108, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 25797, "data": "As of 28 February 2013, Bombardier had delivered five of the 11 trains for Downtown line stage 1.", "label": [[24, 34, "ORG"], [75, 88, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25798, "data": "LTA together with the operator, SBS Transit, conducted the necessary tests to ensure safety standards, functional performance and systems compatibility requirements were met before revenue service began on 22 December 2013.Testing for Stage 2 began on 25 October 2015 and rolling stock that was delivered to Gali Batu Depot commenced service in Stage 1 on 21 October 2015.", "label": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [32, 43, "ORG"], [308, 323, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25800, "data": "A new depot, named the East Coast Integrated Depot, is planned to provide additional stabling capacity to the line in 2024.", "label": [[23, 50, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25801, "data": "The network is additionally scheduled to interchange with the Johor Bahru-Singapore Rapid Transit System that will traverse the Johore Strait once completed, connecting Singapore with the southern Malaysian city of Johor Bahru.", "label": [[62, 104, "FAC"], [128, 141, "LOC"], [169, 178, "LOC"], [215, 226, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25803, "data": "A number of underground stations double as purpose-built air raid shelters under the operational authority of the Singapore Civil Defence Force (SCDF); these stations incorporate deep-level station boxes cast with hardened concrete and blast doors fashioned out of reinforced steel to withstand conventional aerial and chemical ordnance.", "label": [[114, 143, "ORG"], [145, 149, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 25804, "data": "The origins of the Mass Rapid Transit (MRT) are derived from a forecast by city planners in 1967 which stated the need for a rail-based urban transport system by 1992.", "label": [[19, 37, "FAC"], [39, 42, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25805, "data": "The North South Line was given priority because it passed through the Central Area that has a high demand for public transport.", "label": [[4, 20, "FAC"], [70, 82, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25806, "data": "The Mass Rapid Transit Corporation (MRTC) - later renamed SMRT Corporation-was established on 14 October 1983 and took over the roles and responsibilities of the former provisional Mass Rapid Transit Authority.", "label": [[4, 34, "ORG"], [36, 40, "ORG"], [58, 74, "ORG"], [181, 209, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 25812, "data": "The concept of having rail lines that bring people almost directly to their homes led to the introduction of the Light Rail Transit (LRT) lines connecting with the MRT network.", "label": [[113, 131, "FAC"], [133, 136, "FAC"], [164, 167, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25813, "data": "On 6 November 1999, the first LRT trains on the Bukit Panjang LRT went into operation.", "label": [[48, 65, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25816, "data": "The North East Line, the first line operated by SBS Transit, opened on 20 June 2003, is one of the first fully automated heavy rail lines in the world.", "label": [[4, 19, "FAC"], [48, 59, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 25819, "data": "Stage 1 of Downtown line opened on 22 December 2013 with its official opening made on 21 December 2013 by Prime Minister Lee Hsien Loong.", "label": [[11, 24, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25821, "data": "The Tuas West Extension of the East West Line, consisting of Gul Circle, Tuas Crescent, Tuas West Road, and Tuas Link stations, opened on 18 June 2017.", "label": [[4, 23, "FAC"], [31, 45, "FAC"], [61, 71, "LOC"], [73, 86, "LOC"], [88, 102, "LOC"], [108, 117, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25822, "data": "Stage 3, the final stage of the Downtown Line, opened on 21 October 2017 with its official opening made on 20 October 2017 by Coordinating Minister for Infrastructure and Minister for Transport Khaw Boon Wan.", "label": [[32, 45, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25823, "data": "The second infill station, Canberra station opened on 2 November 2019.", "label": [[27, 43, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25824, "data": "Stage 1 of the Thomson-East Coast Line opened on 31 January 2020.", "label": [[15, 38, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25825, "data": "Stage 2 of the Thomson-East Coast Line began operations on 28 August 2021, extending the line from Woodlands South to Caldecott.", "label": [[15, 38, "FAC"], [99, 114, "LOC"], [118, 127, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25827, "data": "The Land Transport Authority (LTA) announced a plan to introduce dual speeds to escalators along the North South and East West lines, to make it safer for senior citizens using them.", "label": [[4, 28, "ORG"], [30, 33, "ORG"], [101, 112, "FAC"], [117, 131, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25830, "data": "Architectural themes became more important only in subsequent stages, and resulted in such designs as the cylindrical station shapes on all stations between Kallang and Pasir Ris except Eunos, and west of Boon Lay, and the perched roofs at Boon Lay, Lakeside, Chinese Garden, Bukit Batok, Bukit Gombak, Choa Chu Kang, Khatib, Yishun, and Eunos stations.", "label": [[157, 164, "LOC"], [169, 178, "LOC"], [186, 191, "LOC"], [205, 213, "LOC"], [240, 248, "LOC"], [250, 258, "LOC"], [260, 274, "LOC"], [276, 287, "LOC"], [289, 301, "LOC"], [303, 316, "LOC"], [318, 324, "LOC"], [326, 332, "LOC"], [338, 343, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25831, "data": "Expo station, located on the Changi Airport branch of the East West Line, is adjacent to the 100,000-square-metre Singapore Expo exhibition facility.", "label": [[0, 12, "LOC"], [29, 50, "FAC"], [58, 72, "FAC"], [114, 128, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25832, "data": "The other station with similar architecture is Dover.", "label": [[47, 52, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25835, "data": "The competition did not require any prior architectural experience from competitors and is acknowledged by the industry as one of the most impartial competitions held in Singapore to date.", "label": [[170, 179, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25839, "data": "The opening of the Woodlands Extension introduced bolder pieces of artwork, such as a 4,000 kg sculpture in Woodlands.", "label": [[19, 38, "FAC"], [108, 117, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25840, "data": "With the opening of the North East line in 2003, a series of artworks under a programme called \"Art in Transit\" were commissioned by the Land Transport Authority (LTA).", "label": [[24, 39, "FAC"], [137, 161, "ORG"], [163, 166, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 25841, "data": "Subsequently, all stations on the North East, Circle and Downtown lines have taken part in this programme during their construction, with additional artworks installed at stations on other MRT lines.", "label": [[34, 44, "FAC"], [46, 52, "FAC"], [57, 70, "FAC"], [189, 192, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25842, "data": "At present, all lines run with fixed-length trains between three and six cars, with the Thomson-East Coast Line using four cars.", "label": [[88, 111, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25843, "data": "Since the system's conception in 1987, all train lines have been powered by the 750 volt DC third rail, with the exception of the North East Line which is powered by 1500 volt DC overhead lines.", "label": [[130, 145, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25844, "data": "The North South and East West lines use an automatic train operation system similar to London Underground's Central line.", "label": [[4, 15, "FAC"], [20, 34, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25845, "data": "As a trial run, luggage racks were installed on the C751B trains to serve travellers on the Changi Airport branch line.", "label": [[92, 118, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25846, "data": "Official sources occasionally refer to the trains of the North South and East West lines as numbered generation trains, with the C151 train being the first and the newest C151C train being the sixth.", "label": [[57, 68, "FAC"], [73, 87, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25848, "data": "The North South Line was upgraded to moving block/CBTC in 2017, and the East West line upgraded in 2018.", "label": [[4, 20, "FAC"], [72, 86, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25851, "data": "The CBTC system also permits for improved braking performance in wet weather as compared to the original fixed-block ATC.All new MRT lines built since the North East Line in 2003 were equipped with CBTC from the outset, and have the capability to be completely driverless and automated, requiring no on-board staffing.", "label": [[129, 132, "FAC"], [155, 170, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25855, "data": "The newer Tuas Depot, opened in 2017, provides the East West Line with its own maintenance facility, while Mandai Depot services trains for the Thomson-East Coast line.", "label": [[10, 20, "LOC"], [144, 167, "FAC"], [51, 65, "FAC"], [107, 119, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25856, "data": "The underground Kim Chuan Depot houses trains for the Circle and Downtown lines, now jointly managed by the two MRT operators.", "label": [[16, 31, "LOC"], [54, 60, "FAC"], [65, 78, "FAC"], [112, 115, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25857, "data": "SBS Transit has three depots: Sengkang Depot houses trains for the North East line, the Sengkang LRT line, and the Punggol LRT line.", "label": [[0, 11, "ORG"], [30, 44, "LOC"], [67, 82, "LOC"], [88, 105, "FAC"], [115, 131, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25858, "data": "Tai Seng Facility Building, connected to and located east of Kim Chuan Depot, is currently used for the Downtown line.", "label": [[0, 26, "LOC"], [61, 76, "LOC"], [104, 117, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25859, "data": "While major operations were shifted to the main Gali Batu Depot in 2015, the Tai Seng Facility Building resumed stabling operations with the extension of the Downtown line in 2017.", "label": [[48, 63, "LOC"], [77, 103, "LOC"], [158, 171, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25861, "data": "Gali Batu Depot is the first MRT depot in Singapore to achieve the certification of Building and Construction Authority (BCA) Green Mark Gold.", "label": [[0, 15, "LOC"], [42, 51, "LOC"], [84, 119, "ORG"], [121, 124, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 25862, "data": "In August 2014, plans for the East Coast Integrated Depot, the world's first four-in-one train and bus depot were announced.", "label": [[30, 57, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25863, "data": "It will be built at Tanah Merah beside the original Changi Depot site to serve the East West, Downtown, and Thomson-East Coast lines.", "label": [[20, 31, "LOC"], [52, 64, "LOC"], [83, 92, "FAC"], [94, 102, "FAC"], [108, 131, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25865, "data": "Rolling stock for the Jurong Region Line will be stabled at both facilities.", "label": [[22, 40, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25866, "data": "Tengah Depot will house the JRL Operations Control Centre and have a bus depot integrated with it to optimise land use.", "label": [[0, 12, "LOC"], [28, 31, "FAC"], [32, 57, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25871, "data": "The 42-kilometre (26 mi), 34 station fully underground Downtown Line connects the north-west and eastern regions of Singapore with a loop travelling through the city center.", "label": [[55, 68, "FAC"], [116, 125, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25873, "data": "An extension from Expo is planned to begin operations in 2024, adding an additional 2.2 kilometres and 2 stations to the line, terminating at Sungei Bedok and interchanging with the Thomson-East Coast line.", "label": [[18, 22, "LOC"], [142, 154, "LOC"], [182, 205, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25874, "data": "Hume is an infill station between Hillview and Beauty World and expected to open by 2025.", "label": [[0, 4, "LOC"], [34, 42, "LOC"], [47, 59, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25875, "data": "Upon Hume's opening, the entire line will be 44 kilometres long and have 37 stations in total.", "label": [[5, 9, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25879, "data": "The other four stages follow suit, with Stage 2 from Springleaf to Caldecott on 28 August 2021, Stage 3 from Mount Pleasant to Gardens by the Bay in 2022 (excluding Mount Pleasant and Marina South, which will open at a later date), Stage 4 from Tanjong Rhu to Bayshore in 2024 and Stage 5 from Bedok South to Sungei Bedok in 2025.", "label": [[53, 63, "LOC"], [67, 76, "LOC"], [109, 123, "LOC"], [127, 145, "LOC"], [165, 179, "LOC"], [184, 196, "LOC"], [245, 256, "LOC"], [260, 268, "LOC"], [294, 305, "LOC"], [309, 321, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25880, "data": "The northern terminus of Woodlands North is expected to interchange with the Johor Bahru-Singapore Rapid Transit System to provide access to Johor Bahru and the future Iskandar Malaysia Bus Rapid Transit.", "label": [[25, 40, "LOC"], [77, 119, "FAC"], [141, 152, "LOC"], [168, 203, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25881, "data": "Founders' Memorial station is an infill station along Stage 4, but is scheduled to instead open in tandem with the Founders' Memorial in 2027.", "label": [[0, 26, "LOC"], [115, 133, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25882, "data": "In addition, this line and the Canberra MRT Station was the first to use Top-Up Kiosks (TUK) that only allows cashless payments, while GTMs were retained for traditional modes of payment.", "label": [[31, 51, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25883, "data": "Line extension to Changi AirportIn addition to the previously announced alignment of the Thomson-East Coast Line, an extension has been proposed to connect it to Changi Airport, with the line passing through Terminal 5, and eventually absorbing the existing Changi Airport branch on the East West line.", "label": [[17, 32, "LOC"], [89, 112, "FAC"], [162, 176, "LOC"], [208, 218, "LOC"], [258, 279, "FAC"], [287, 301, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25885, "data": "First proposed as an LRT line when originally announced in 2001, the 20-kilometre (12 mi) Jurong Region Line has since been upgraded to be a medium capacity line after the project was revived in 2013.", "label": [[90, 108, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25887, "data": "Besides the original announced alignment of the line, a West Coast extension to the Circle Line from the Jurong Region Line is currently under study, linking the West Coast region directly to Haw Par Villa, and allowing commuters on the Jurong Region line access to the central area of the city easily.", "label": [[56, 76, "FAC"], [84, 95, "FAC"], [105, 123, "FAC"], [162, 172, "LOC"], [192, 205, "LOC"], [237, 255, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25889, "data": "In addition, the extension to Punggol consists of three stations spanning 7.3 kilometers, and is planned to be completed by 2032.", "label": [[30, 37, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25890, "data": "The 4-kilometre (2.5 mi) extension Stage 6 from Marina Bay through Keppel, ending at HarbourFront, effectively completes the circle and links the current ends of the line, allowing for through service through the future Southern Waterfront City without the need to change to other lines.", "label": [[48, 58, "LOC"], [67, 73, "LOC"], [85, 97, "LOC"], [220, 244, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25892, "data": "Originally scheduled to be completed by 2030, the 1.6-kilometre (0.99 mi) North East Line Extension is being built from Punggol through Punggol North including the new Punggol Downtown to the new tentatively named Punggol Coast station.", "label": [[74, 99, "FAC"], [120, 127, "LOC"], [136, 149, "LOC"], [168, 184, "LOC"], [214, 235, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25897, "data": "However, the Public Transport Council (PTC) announced in 2016 that fares for the three underground lines would be reduced to match those on the NSEWL, which took effect along with the yearly-applied fare changes, on 30 December 2016.After the opening of Downtown line Stage 3, Transport Minister Khaw Boon Wan announced that public transport fare rules will be reviewed to allow for transfers across MRT lines at different stations due to the increasing density of the rail network.", "label": [[13, 37, "ORG"], [39, 42, "ORG"], [144, 149, "FAC"], [254, 267, "FAC"], [400, 403, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25900, "data": "On 5 August 1993, two trains collided at Clementi station because of an oil spillage on the track, which resulted in 132 injuries.", "label": [[41, 57, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25902, "data": "On 15 November 2017, at 8:20 am, two trains collided at Joo Koon station, injuring 36 passengers and 2 SMRT staff.", "label": [[56, 72, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25903, "data": "For the December 2011 disruptions, the Land Transport Authority imposed a maximum punishment of S$2 million on SMRT (approximately US$1.526 million) for the two train disruptions along the North South Line on 15 and 17 December 2011.", "label": [[39, 63, "ORG"], [111, 115, "ORG"], [189, 205, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25904, "data": "Independent experts from Sweden and Japan were hired to conduct investigation into the cause of the disruption.", "label": [[25, 31, "LOC"], [36, 41, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25905, "data": "For the July 2015 disruption, LTA imposed a higher penalty of S$5.4 million on SMRT.", "label": [[30, 33, "ORG"], [79, 83, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 25907, "data": "The operator said the team had permission to access the tracks, but did not coordinate with a signal unit in the station control to ensure train captains in the area where the team was exercised caution while pulling into Pasir Ris station.", "label": [[222, 239, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25909, "data": "Urban transport expert Park Byung Joon from the Singapore University of Social Sciences added that the negligence displayed by SMRT in this regard was tantamount to a criminal offence, and after an internal investigation, found that the maintenance crew of the Bishan Station's pump system had submitted maintenance records for nearly a year without actually carrying out the works.", "label": [[48, 87, "ORG"], [127, 131, "ORG"], [261, 275, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25911, "data": "By July 2019, the Mean Kilometres Between Failure (MKBF) for the North South and East West lines had jumped to 700,000 km and 1,400,000 km respectively.", "label": [[65, 76, "FAC"], [81, 95, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25913, "data": "In 2005, the Singapore Police Force announced plans to step up rail security by establishing a specialised security unit for public transport, then known as the Police MRT unit.", "label": [[13, 35, "ORG"], [161, 176, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 25914, "data": "The unit today expanded to become Public Transport Security Command (TRANSCOM) since 2009.", "label": [[34, 67, "ORG"], [69, 77, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 25915, "data": "In January 2006, Exercise Northstar V involved over 2,000 personnel from 22 government agencies responding to simulated bombings and chemical attacks at Dhoby Ghaut, Toa Payoh, Raffles Place and Marina Bay stations.", "label": [[153, 164, "LOC"], [166, 175, "LOC"], [177, 190, "LOC"], [195, 213, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25916, "data": "In August 2013, Exercise Greyhound tested the response of SBS Transit's Operations Control Centre and the implementation of its contingency plans for bus bridging, free bus service and deployment of goodwill ambassadors (GAs) during a simulated prolonged train service disruption.", "label": [[58, 69, "ORG"], [72, 97, "FAC"]]}
{"id": 25919, "data": "Measures were put in place by the Public Transport Security Committee to enhance depot security in light of the first incident, but works were yet to be completed by SMRT Corporation when the second incident, on 17 August 2011, occurred at Bishan Depot.", "label": [[34, 69, "ORG"], [166, 182, "ORG"], [240, 252, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25921, "data": "Singapore has a total land area of 724.2 square kilometres (279.6 sq mi).The Singapore area comprises mainland and other islands.", "label": [[0, 9, "LOC"], [76, 86, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25924, "data": "Singapore's main territory is a diamond-shaped island, although its territory includes surrounding smaller islands.", "label": [[0, 9, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25925, "data": "The farthest outlying island is Pedra Branca.", "label": [[32, 44, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25926, "data": "Of Singapore's dozens of smaller islands, Jurong Island, Pulau Tekong, Pulau Ubin and Sentosa are the larger ones.", "label": [[3, 12, "LOC"], [42, 55, "LOC"], [57, 69, "LOC"], [71, 81, "LOC"], [86, 93, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25927, "data": "Most of Singapore is no more than 15 metres above sea level.", "label": [[8, 17, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25929, "data": "Singapore has no natural lakes, but reservoirs and water catchment areas have been constructed to store fresh water for Singapore's water supply.", "label": [[0, 9, "LOC"], [120, 129, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25931, "data": "Singapore is one-and-a-half degrees north of the equator, lying entirely between the 1st and 2nd parallels.", "label": [[0, 9, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25934, "data": "May is the hottest month of the year in Singapore, followed by June.", "label": [[40, 49, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25938, "data": "This is significant to note because even a small hill such as Bukit Timah Hill can cause this phenomenon.", "label": [[62, 78, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25942, "data": "Singapore is the first country in Southeast Asia to levy a carbon tax, at $5 per ton, applicable for its largest carbon-emitting corporations that produce more than 25,000 tons of carbon dioxide per year.", "label": [[0, 9, "LOC"], [34, 48, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25946, "data": "Gabbro is also found in the area and is found in an area called Little Guilin named for its resemblance to Guilin in Southern China.", "label": [[64, 77, "LOC"], [107, 113, "LOC"], [126, 131, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25947, "data": "This area is in Bukit Gombak.", "label": [[16, 28, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25949, "data": "Metamorphic rocks are found in the northeastern part of Singapore and also on Pulau Tekong off the east coast of Singapore.", "label": [[56, 65, "LOC"], [78, 90, "LOC"], [113, 122, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25950, "data": "Singapore is relatively safe from seismic activity in the region, as the nearest major active faults are hundreds of kilometres away in Indonesia.", "label": [[0, 9, "LOC"], [136, 145, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25953, "data": "When Singapore was first colonized by the British, the City of Singapore was situated on the southern coast, around the mouth of the Singapore River.", "label": [[5, 14, "LOC"], [63, 72, "LOC"], [133, 148, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25954, "data": "This area remains the Central Area of Singapore.", "label": [[22, 34, "LOC"], [38, 47, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25956, "data": "Politically, Singapore is divided into five administrative districts, these are then further subdivided into town councils which usually consists of one or more political constituencies.", "label": [[13, 22, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25957, "data": "However, unlike other countries where local government subdivisions are used to cite locations, the same practice is often uncommon in Singapore.", "label": [[135, 144, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25958, "data": "Planning and census boundaries, called planning areas, have been used by the Urban Redevelopment Authority to define certain districts and neighbourhoods, although these boundaries may not necessarily correspond with the common perception of a certain place.", "label": [[77, 106, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 25959, "data": "Tiong Bahru for example, is often identified separately from the HDB town it is a part of, Bukit Merah.", "label": [[0, 11, "LOC"], [65, 68, "ORG"], [91, 102, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25962, "data": "However, to reduce strain on the Central Area, several regional centres have been developed, each containing a concentrated commercial district.", "label": [[33, 45, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25965, "data": "In the north there is a causeway for both rail and road traffic, which connects to the city of Johor Bahru.", "label": [[95, 106, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25968, "data": "It was started in 1909 as a railway link by Johor State Railway to connect Johor Bahru to Singapore, then the administrative headquarters of British interests in Southeast Asia.", "label": [[44, 63, "ORG"], [75, 86, "LOC"], [90, 99, "LOC"], [162, 176, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25970, "data": "This has led to disagreements with Malaysia.", "label": [[35, 43, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25972, "data": "Since Singapore lacks natural freshwater rivers and lakes, the primary source of domestic water is rainfall.", "label": [[6, 15, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25974, "data": "To lessen its reliance on imports, Singapore has built reservoirs to collect rainwater from both forest catchment and urban catchment run-offs and from recycled water facilities.", "label": [[35, 44, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25975, "data": "In addition, Singapore has built three desalination plants on the western coast of Tuas with two more under construction.", "label": [[13, 22, "LOC"], [83, 87, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25976, "data": "They are expected to at least meet 30% of Singapore's water demands in 2060.", "label": [[42, 51, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25978, "data": "Because of this, Singapore is also commonly known as the 'Garden City'.", "label": [[17, 26, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25980, "data": "Transport within Singapore is mainly land-based.", "label": [[17, 26, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25981, "data": "Many parts of Singapore, including islands such as Sentosa and Jurong Island are accessible by road.", "label": [[14, 23, "LOC"], [51, 58, "LOC"], [63, 76, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25982, "data": "The other major form of transportation within Singapore is rail: the Mass Rapid Transit which runs the length and width of Singapore, and the Light Rail Transit which runs within a few neighbourhoods.", "label": [[46, 55, "LOC"], [69, 87, "FAC"], [142, 160, "FAC"], [123, 132, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25983, "data": "The main island of Singapore is connected to the other islands by ferryboat services.", "label": [[19, 28, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25984, "data": "There are two bridges which link Singapore to Malaysia - the Causeway, and the Second Link.", "label": [[33, 42, "LOC"], [46, 54, "LOC"], [61, 69, "LOC"], [79, 90, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25985, "data": "The Singapore Changi Airport is a major aviation hub in Asia.", "label": [[4, 28, "LOC"], [56, 60, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25986, "data": "Singapore is also notable for being one of the world's busiest transshipment ports.", "label": [[0, 9, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25988, "data": "Singapore also has one of the most cost-efficient public transport networks in the world, according to a study by London consulting firm Credo.", "label": [[0, 9, "LOC"], [137, 142, "ORG"], [114, 120, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25989, "data": "With the emergence of driverless vehicles, Singapore is now among the favourite locations for autonomous vehicles development testing location for the big players in the automotive industry.", "label": [[43, 52, "LOC"]]}
{"id": 25991, "data": "There are more than 365 scheduled bus services, operated by SBS Transit, SMRT Buses, Tower Transit Singapore and Go-Ahead Singapore.", "label": [[60, 71, "ORG"], [73, 83, "ORG"], [85, 108, "ORG"], [113, 131, "ORG"]]}
