{"id":2020,"text":"Speaking at a break fast event organised by the Islamic Religious Council of Singapore (MUIS) at the Al-Muttaqin Mosque in Ang Mo Kio, PM Lee noted that more Muslims have been able to visit mosques, with Friday, and tarawih or nightly prayers returning to near-normal for the first time since Covid-19.","label":[[48,86,"ORG"],[88,92,"ORG"],[101,119,"LOC"],[123,133,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2021,"text":"16-year-old Serangoon Gardens Secondary School student, Muhammad Syafiq Mohd Sukairi, has been volunteering with Al-Muttaqin Mosque in Ang Mo Kio, helping out with terawih preparations.","label":[[12,46,"ORG"],[113,131,"ORG"],[135,145,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2022,"text":"Staff and volunteers of Masjid Al-Muttaqin having chicken rice and other snacks to break their fast.","label":[[24,42,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2024,"text":"Outside Ghufran Mosque in Tampines on April 24, a queue formed before the porridge distribution, which started at 5pm.","label":[[8,22,"LOC"],[26,34,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2025,"text":"As part of the effort to reach out to more people, Ghufran Mosque distributes almost half of its daily porridge portion at Our Tampines Hub (OTH), which is next to the mosque.","label":[[51,65,"ORG"],[123,139,"LOC"],[141,144,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2026,"text":"Completed in December 1990, Masjid Darul Ghufran serves as a focal point for the Muslim community in Tampines.","label":[[28,48,"LOC"],[101,109,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2027,"text":"Free Adult Islamic Learning courses are being offered by Masjid Darul Ghufran.","label":[[57,77,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2028,"text":"UNIQLO's first neighbourhood store that will pilot community partnership projects and sustainability initiatives will open its doors at 51 @ Ang Mo Kio, a standalone building nestled in Ang Mo Kio Avenue 3.","label":[[0,6,"ORG"],[136,151,"LOC"],[186,205,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2029,"text":"Dear sirs, may I know if the HDB Ang Mo Kio Branch Office wil be open from 2 Jun 20 onward?","label":[[29,32,"ORG"],[33,57,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2030,"text":"In response, the hawker at 409 Ang Mo Kio Market & Food Centre told a Shin Min Daily News reporter that the accusation that she was trying to literally make a quick buck off the 13-year-old girl was not right.","label":[[27,62,"LOC"],[70,89,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2033,"text":"A woman in Singapore ordered seven drinks from the Starbucks outlet at AMK Hub, but all the beverages were found spilled on the public pedestrian footpath near the delivery address without any explanation as the delivery rider became uncontactable after marking the order delivered.","label":[[11,20,"LOC"],[51,60,"ORG"],[71,78,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2034,"text":"The Weights and Measures Office said on Feb 11 that the weighing instruments at FairPrice's NEX and AMK Hub branches have been inspected and verified to be accurate.","label":[[4,31,"ORG"],[80,90,"ORG"],[92,95,"LOC"],[100,107,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2035,"text":"The incident happened with a raw chicken breast from a FairPrice Xtra at NEX shopping mall in Serangoon on Feb 5 and a piece of fresh salmon from AMK Hub's FairPrice outlet on Feb 7.","label":[[55,69,"ORG"],[73,76,"LOC"],[146,153,"LOC"],[156,165,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2036,"text":"Based on the initial assessment from the video, the mislabelling incident which occurred at our store at FairPrice Xtra @ Ang Mo Kio Hub is likely caused by human error.","label":[[105,119,"ORG"],[122,136,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2037,"text":"Merchandise produced by APSN will be sold on Ang Mo Kio Town Council's Facebook page and website for $5 to $10 each, with all proceeds going to the social service agency.","label":[[24,28,"ORG"],[45,68,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2038,"text":"Two special education schools serving students with mild intellectual disability will move to an expanded, co-located campus in 2025, the Ministry of Education (MOE) said on Thursday (Nov 5). They are Chaoyang School in Ang Mo Kio, which serves primary school students, and Tanglin School in Bukit Merah serving secondary school students.","label":[[138,159,"ORG"],[161,164,"ORG"],[201,216,"ORG"],[220,230,"LOC"],[274,288,"ORG"],[292,303,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2039,"text":"Both schools will move to a new site at the former Da Qiao Primary School in Ang Mo Kio, MOE said in a press release. Student capacity will be expanded with the redevelopment, with Chaoyang Sch to provide 400 places and Tanglin Sch to provide 350 places.","label":[[51,73,"LOC"],[77,87,"LOC"],[181,193,"ORG"],[220,231,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2040,"text":"The police have issued warnings to six people for their role in a protest without a permit outside the Ministry of Education Headquarters in Buona Vista in January this year.","label":[[103,137,"LOC"],[141,152,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2041,"text":"The protest outside MOE HQ happened after a transgender pre-university student diagnosed with gender dysphoria said in a Reddit post in January that the MOE had blocked her from getting hormonal treatment.","label":[[20,26,"LOC"],[153,156,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2043,"text":"Ms Jacelyn Lim, executive director of Autism Resource Centre (Singapore), said more can be done beyond raising awareness. The Autism Resource Centre is co-located with Pathlight School at Ang Mo Kio Ave 10.","label":[[38,72,"ORG"],[126,148,"ORG"],[168,184,"ORG"],[188,205,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2046,"text":"Pathlight School is the first autism-focused school in Singapore that offers Singapore's national curriculum together with life readiness skills.","label":[[0,16,"ORG"],[55,64,"LOC"],[77,86,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2048,"text":"After her A Levels, Ms Sum initially wanted to pursue Psychology in an overseas university in Australia or in the United Kingdom (UK), but a friend told her about the Psychology programme offered by the James Cook University's Singapore campus.","label":[[94,103,"LOC"],[114,128,"LOC"],[130,132,"LOC"],[203,224,"ORG"],[227,236,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2049,"text":"Mishel, 16, who is from Madrasah Al-Arabiah Al-Islamiah in Toa Payoh, got eight A1s for subjects like pure physics, pure chemistry and pure biology, and one A2 for additional mathematics.","label":[[24,55,"ORG"],[59,68,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2050,"text":"In December, Mishel finished a six-week internship at the NanoBio Lab at the Agency for Science, Technology and Research or A*Star, and now plans to sign up for a bio-medical course at a polytechnic.","label":[[58,69,"ORG"],[77,120,"ORG"],[124,130,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2051,"text":"The trio from DPS International School, together with seven friends from school, decided to collect food donations from their schoolmates to donate to food charity Food From The Heart for distribution to the needy.","label":[[14,38,"ORG"],[164,183,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2052,"text":"Among the other winners was a team from Singapore Chinese Girls' School, which rolled out an Instagram campaign to promote a kampung spirit among Singaporeans.","label":[[40,71,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2054,"text":"Minutes after CHIJ St Nicholas Girls' School won the North Zone B Division girls' table tennis title on Thursday (April 21), team vice-captain Chia Chern Yee burst into tears even though she did not feature in the final. The teenager could not contain her emotions after going through a roller-coaster year with the team, who failed to retain their title last year as they finished runners-up to Yishun Town Secondary School. So it was sweet revenge for CHIJ St Nick's at CHIJ St Joseph's Convent on Thursday as they beat YTSS 3-2 to regain the B Division trophy.","label":[[14,44,"ORG"],[396,424,"ORG"],[454,466,"ORG"],[472,496,"LOC"],[522,526,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2055,"text":"In the boys' final, it was business as usual for Catholic High School (CHS) who retained their B Division title after beating YTSS 3-2. It was a case of deja vu for CHS' Arifin Zulkarnain, who also played in the decider in last year's finals against Maris Stella High School.","label":[[49,69,"ORG"],[71,74,"ORG"],[126,130,"ORG"],[165,168,"ORG"],[250,274,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2057,"text":"Ang Mo Kio Town Council's Kebun Baru Office is located next to Mayflower Market & Food Centre.","label":[[0,23,"ORG"],[26,43,"LOC"],[63,93,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2058,"text":"Not many know this, but the Alzheimer's Disease Association started this Wayfinding Project to use murals for a practical purpose: They transformed the Kebun Baru neighbourhood into a dementia-friendly neighbourhood by painting distinct, brightly coloured objects on select void deck walls of each block in Kebun Baru View and Kebun Baru Heights.","label":[[28,59,"ORG"],[152,162,"LOC"],[307,322,"LOC"],[327,345,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2059,"text":"He was a volunteer and committee member of the Jin Ying Tang Temple, giving his time to help out at events. He broke into Jin Ying Tang Temple in Ang Mo Kio on more than 60 occasions.","label":[[47,67,"ORG"],[122,142,"LOC"],[146,156,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2060,"text":"Called the Integrated Dementia (Home-based) Assisted Living, or IDeAL@115, the project is a partnership between Kebun Baru Grassroots Organisations and social service agency Dementia Singapore.","label":[[112,147,"ORG"],[174,192,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2061,"text":"A freehold strata-titled development at 50 Tagore Lane is on the market at a guide price of $100 million, according to Cushman & Wakefield (C&W), which is marketing the property.","label":[[40,54,"LOC"],[119,138,"ORG"],[140,143,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2062,"text":"At Springleaf station - which serves the neighbouring Springleaf and Thong Soon estates - commuters are greeted by a towering banyan tree, adorning the elevator shaft connecting the concourse and platform levels of the station.","label":[[3,21,"LOC"],[54,64,"LOC"],[69,79,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2063,"text":"For his artwork Interlude for Lentor, artist Tan Guo-Liang told reporters he was inspired by memories of visits to his aunt who lived at Teachers'Estate, adjacent to Lentor station.","label":[[30,36,"LOC"],[137,152,"LOC"],[166,180,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2064,"text":"For Caldecott station - which serves as an interchange station with the Circle Line - artist Claire Lim was inspired by the station's location near the Singapore Association of the Visually Handicapped and the Lighthouse School to create her art piece using Braille.","label":[[4,21,"LOC"],[72,83,"FAC"],[152,201,"LOC"],[210,227,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2066,"text":"SSP's student-athletes won 10 out of the 24 medals across the cadet (Under-17) men's and women's sabre, epee and foil competitions, winning half of the six gold medals on offer. Two of those wins came on Wednesday at the OCBC Arena Hall 6.","label":[[0,3,"ORG"],[221,238,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2067,"text":"After watching teammate Nabihah Raiedah Mohammad Fadly pick up the cadet women's foil title with a 15-4 win over Crescent Girls' School's Trina Soh, SSP fencer Isaac Ong claimed the cadet sabre gold.","label":[[113,135,"ORG"],[149,152,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2071,"text":"In another circular on Monday, Pei Chun Public School told parents that a third student had tested positive for Covid-19. This student had been swabbed as part of a testing operation for those who had been in close contact with one of two other pupils who had earlier contracted the disease.","label":[[31,53,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2072,"text":"If the two cases also happened to be close contacts of separate Covid-19 cases outside school, such as within their own households, then it would be more likely that they were infected at home, said Dr Alex Cook, an associate professor at the National University of Singapore's Saw Swee Hock School of Public Health.","label":[[243,275,"ORG"],[278,315,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2074,"text":"Dr Paul Tambyah, president of the Asia Pacific Society of Clinical Microbiology and Infection, said that further phylogenetic studies - or molecular analyses - will have to be completed to categorically rule out any school-based transmission.","label":[[34,93,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2075,"text":"Some 600 households from four Housing and Development Board (HDB) blocks located along Ang Mo Kio Avenue 3 will undergo the Selective En-Bloc Redevelopment Scheme, with residents given the option move to a new housing estate on Ang Mo Kio Drive.","label":[[30,59,"ORG"],[61,64,"ORG"],[87,106,"LOC"],[228,244,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2077,"text":"The last SERS exercise was carried out in 2018 for Blocks 81 to 83 on MacPherson Lane, with replacement flats along Circuit Road expected to be completed by the second quarter of next year.","label":[[51,66,"LOC"],[70,85,"LOC"],[116,128,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2078,"text":"HDB added that owners of the eligible flats on Ang Mo Kio Avenue 3 will be compensated based on the market value of their flats as assessed by a professional private valuer it appoints.","label":[[0,3,"ORG"],[47,66,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2080,"text":"They can also select replacement flats together with their neighbours or relatives, to live near one another, HDB said. In this way, SERS helps to preserve existing community ties by enabling residents to move en-bloc to new replacement flats.","label":[[110,113,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2081,"text":"Residents of the selected blocks may also attend a SERS sharing session at the void deck of Block 564 on April 9 and 10 from 9.30am to 5.15pm, or between April 11 and 14 from 1pm to 8.45pm.","label":[[92,101,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2082,"text":"Asked why the four blocks were possibly chosen, Ms Christine Sun, senior vice-president of research and analytics at real estate agency OrangeTee & Tie, said that the land parcel may not be fully optimised at the moment.","label":[[136,151,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2083,"text":"\"I think that piece of land could be redeveloped into a few tall blocks, which may even be an integrated development comprising some retail or commercial components linked to the Tavistock MRT Station, Ms Sun added.","label":[[179,200,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2085,"text":"From there, residents will have convenient access to both Ang Mo Kio MRT Station and Yio Chu Kang MRT Station, as well as to shops and eateries such as the Cheng San Market and Cooked Food Centre.","label":[[58,80,"LOC"],[85,109,"LOC"],[156,195,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2086,"text":"Eligible flat owners may also receive a SERS grant of up to S$30,000 for families, or S$15,000 for singles, and take out a housing loan from HDB to buy their replacement flat.","label":[[141,144,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2087,"text":"Seems like AMKSS is a better choice than Presbyterian High or Chung Cheng High School Yishun.","label":[[11,16,"ORG"],[41,58,"ORG"],[62,92,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2090,"text":"AMKSS dancers are very good. Comparable to SOTA.","label":[[0,5,"ORG"],[43,47,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2092,"text":"Heard he was one of the teachers that helped Xinmin Sec moved up sch ranking to top sch before posted to another neighborhood sch in AMK - think Yio Chu Kang Secondary.","label":[[45,55,"ORG"],[133,136,"LOC"],[145,167,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2095,"text":"Such a welcomed treat for our residents at St Luke's ElderCare Residence @ Ang Mo Kio! Volunteers from Cycling Without Age Singapore brought elders Mr Lim, Mdm Loh and Mdm Koon out for their first outdoor trip to Bishan-Ang Mo Kio Park in a long while.","label":[[43,85,"LOC"],[103,132,"ORG"],[213,235,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2096,"text":"The 66-year-old from St Luke's ElderCare Residence @ Ang Mo Kio, who uses a wheelchair, said of the outing at Bishan-Ang Mo Kio Park: \"I'm happy to be going out again.\"","label":[[21,63,"LOC"],[110,132,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2098,"text":"Residents from St Luke's ElderCare Residence and Sree Narayana Mission in Yishun will be the first to get to go on rides every week in the neighbourhood.","label":[[15,44,"LOC"],[49,70,"LOC"],[74,80,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2100,"text":"Ms Cecilia Llego, a senior physiotherapist from St Luke's ElderCare Residence @ Ang Mo Kio, said the seniors were excited to chat with the nursing home staff and cyclist volunteers, and point out familiar landmarks around the park.","label":[[48,90,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2101,"text":"St Luke's ElderCare Residence cares for seniors above 50 who are medically stable but have undergone post-operative procedures for strokes, fractures or falls.","label":[[0,29,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2103,"text":"Ms Poon said that she lives with her mother in Bishan, about a 15-minute walk from the Bishan ActiveSG Gym, which has equipment suitable for the elderly.","label":[[47,53,"LOC"],[87,106,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2104,"text":"Other locations include Senja-Cashew CC, Fernvale CC and Pek Kio CC, he added.","label":[[24,39,"LOC"],[41,52,"LOC"],[57,67,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2105,"text":"Bishan Community Club and Ang Mo Kio Community Centre each had three of these vending machines.","label":[[0,21,"LOC"],[26,53,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2106,"text":"Mr Connor Gan, 24, who owns a food and beverage business, was wearing the reusable mask from the previous collection exercise when he went to Bishan CC on Tuesday.","label":[[142,151,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2107,"text":"The new adult-size masks are produced by textile manufacturer Ghim Li in collaboration with Nanyang Technological University, while the child-size ones are by textile firm Ramatex and the Agency for Science, Technology and Research.","label":[[62,69,"ORG"],[92,124,"ORG"],[172,179,"ORG"],[188,231,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2113,"text":"\"The cancellation of masses does not mean that Catholics can excuse themselves from fulfilling the obligation of keeping the Day of the Lord holy,\" he said.","label":[]}
{"id":2114,"text":"On Friday, MOH announced that one of the coronavirus cases announced on Thursday had previously attended mass at Church of Christ the King, a Catholic parish in Ang Mo Kio.","label":[[113,138,"LOC"],[161,171,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2115,"text":"Some Protestant churches have also stopped services at their physical locations temporarily.","label":[]}
{"id":2116,"text":"One of Singapore's largest churches, City Harvest Church, will be playing its services online for the rest of February.","label":[[37,56,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2117,"text":"Grace Assembly of God, where a cluster of 13 confirmed coronavirus cases are linked to, has closed both its branches until Feb 25.","label":[[0,21,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2118,"text":"Christian and Buddhist groups have begun to record their services and rituals in light of the COVID-19 outbreak, while the Islamic Religious Council of Singapore (MUIS) has also encouraged mosques to do so for events.","label":[[123,161,"ORG"],[163,167,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2119,"text":"Every Nation Church and Paya Lebar Methodist Church are two of the churches that will broadcast their upcoming Sunday services and mass virtually.","label":[[0,19,"ORG"],[24,51,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2120,"text":"Paya Lebar Methodist Church has been linked to one confirmed case, but church volunteers had already been taking the temperatures of congregants, cleaning the premises more frequently, and keeping a record of their data for contact tracing purposes since MOH first issued its guidelines, said pastor-in-charge Rev Dr Kow Shih Ming.","label":[[0,27,"ORG"],[255,258,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2121,"text":"The Buddha Tooth Relic Temple at Chinatown is livestreaming its ceremonies and group practices on its website, according to a letter it sent out on Feb 12.","label":[[4,29,"ORG"],[33,42,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2122,"text":"Singapore was ranked the world's most expensive city for the second year running by the Economist Intelligence Unit (EIU) on March 2.","label":[[0,9,"LOC"],[88,115,"ORG"],[117,120,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2124,"text":"To name a few, Parkway Parade offers shoppers shuttle buses to and from Bedok and Sengkang on weekends and public holidays, while Marina Square in City Hall allows a hungry lunchtime crowd to catch a free ride from Clifford Pier, TheSail@Marina Bay and Marina Bay Financial Centre from 11.30am to 2.30pm on weekdays.","label":[[15,29,"ORG"],[72,77,"LOC"],[82,90,"LOC"],[130,143,"ORG"],[147,156,"LOC"],[215,228,"LOC"],[230,248,"LOC"],[253,280,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2126,"text":"Free parking is available at City Square Mall in Kitchener Road for the first 1.5 hours during the weekday lunchtime period between 12pm and 2pm, while IMM Building in Jurong East offers two hours of free parking upon entry every day.","label":[[29,45,"LOC"],[49,63,"LOC"],[152,164,"ORG"],[168,179,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2127,"text":"Deen Restaurant at 803 King George's Avenue still sells plain prata at 80 cents apiece.","label":[[0,15,"ORG"],[19,43,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2129,"text":"It's $3 a bowl on average at most stalls, according to a survey of 503 hawker stalls by the Consumers Association of Singapore (CASE) last year.","label":[[92,126,"ORG"],[128,132,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2130,"text":"A plate of rice with two choices of vegetables and one meat costs $2.50 at Fei Zai Mixed Vegetable Rice Porridge in Maxwell Food Centre in Kadayanallur Street.","label":[[75,112,"ORG"],[116,135,"LOC"],[139,158,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2133,"text":"The Ang Mo Kio branch of the Singapore Buddhist Free Clinic is located at 348 Ang Mo Kio Ave 3 Singapore 560348.","label":[[4,21,"LOC"],[29,59,"ORG"],[74,111,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2135,"text":"The Public Free Clinic Society, which also specialises in TCM, provides free consultation, charges $2 for registration per session. Thye Hua Kwan and the Chung Hwa Medical Institution also provide medical services for free or at low rates.","label":[[4,30,"ORG"],[132,145,"ORG"],[154,183,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2136,"text":"A basic health insurance policy in Singapore costs US$90.50 (S$113.20) annually, according to Deutsche Bank.","label":[[35,44,"LOC"],[94,107,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2138,"text":"As part of its community outreach programme, the Singapore Symphony Orchestra (SSO) holds free concerts at outdoor locations such as Botanic Gardens and Gardens By The Bay, and indoor ones at lunchtime.","label":[[49,77,"ORG"],[79,82,"ORG"],[133,148,"LOC"],[153,171,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2141,"text":"The Science Centre Singapore organises free stargazing sessions every Friday evening.","label":[[4,28,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2143,"text":"The outdoor play area at Gardens By The Bay, the boardwalk atop VivoCity, and Changi Airport, which provides materials for children to do art, are some places popular with the young ones. East Coast Park is another good place for children to enjoy. You can also \"park\" your children at free play areas in shopping centres such as Marina Square.","label":[[25,43,"LOC"],[64,72,"LOC"],[78,92,"LOC"],[188,203,"LOC"],[330,343,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2144,"text":"Visit Supertree Grove at Gardens By The Bay for free - going instead into the Cloud Forest or Flower Dome will cost money - Singaporeans pay $20 to visit the two conservatories, while foreigners pay $28. The mega park, which cost $1 billion to build, features more than 2,000 plant species from nearly every continent and 18 Supertrees, which are vertical gardens up to 50m tall.","label":[[6,21,"LOC"],[25,43,"LOC"],[78,90,"LOC"],[94,105,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2145,"text":"Admission to the Botanic Gardens, which is applying to qualify as Singapore's first UNESCO World Heritage site, is free. But just don't try to climb onto the legendary Tembusu tree which is more than two centuries old.","label":[[17,32,"LOC"],[66,75,"LOC"],[84,90,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2146,"text":"The 56th level of ION Orchard, 218m above ground, allows anyone to admire the buildings that dot the country from up above. Admission into the Ion Sky observatory is free.","label":[[18,29,"LOC"],[143,162,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2147,"text":"The rooftop of the Esplanade and the open-air sky garden at National Library are also places to enjoy Singapore's skyline.","label":[[19,28,"LOC"],[60,76,"LOC"],[102,111,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2151,"text":"Haw Par Villa - owned by the Myanmar-Chinese Aw brothers of Tiger Balm ointment fame - used to be popular among families and tourists because of its 1,000 statues depicting scenes from Chinese folklore, including the well-known \"10 courts of hell\". It made a comeback recently as part of the Singapore Tourism Board's Tourism50 campaign to encourage Singaporeans to visit local attractions.","label":[[0,13,"LOC"],[292,315,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2156,"text":"Visiting the Chong Pang City Wet Market is a daily routine for housewife Sum Kwai Siong, but the risk of Covid-19 infections from crowds expected over Chinese New Year is keeping her on edge.","label":[[13,39,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2158,"text":"The Sunday Times visited the Chong Pang City Wet Market on Thursday (Feb 4) and the Teck Ghee Court Market and Food Centre on Friday (Feb 5).","label":[[29,55,"LOC"],[84,122,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2159,"text":"Safe-distancing posters and bright red and yellow floor markers to indicate one-metre distancing were seen around the Chong Pang Market and SafeEntry QR codes were at the main entrance.","label":[[118,135,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2161,"text":"The Land Transport Authority (LTA) has awarded a contract worth $615.9 million for the construction of the North-South Corridor, a 21.5km expressway which will connect towns in the north to the city centre.","label":[[4,28,"ORG"],[30,33,"ORG"],[107,127,"FAC"]]}
{"id":2162,"text":"As part of the contract, Shanghai Tunnel Engineering Co (Singapore) will construct a road tunnel, the Teck Ghee MRT station box and commuter facilities such as pedestrian overhead bridges between Sin Ming Avenue and Ang Mo Kio Avenue 3.","label":[[25,67,"ORG"],[102,123,"LOC"],[196,211,"LOC"],[216,235,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2163,"text":"The 800m-long road tunnel will feature a pair of three-lane roads. It will be integrated with the planned Teck Ghee station on the future Cross Island Line.","label":[[106,123,"LOC"],[138,155,"FAC"]]}
{"id":2164,"text":"The organisers said the number of participants rehearsing at the floating platform has been reduced by about 70 per cent compared with previous years. Some are also some rehearsing at satellite sites at Jewel Changi Airport, the National University of Singapore and Yio Chu Kang Stadium.","label":[[203,223,"LOC"],[229,261,"LOC"],[266,286,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2166,"text":"The court heard that Shanmugam was assigned to perform night shift maintenance work at Ang Mo Kio Police Division Headquarters with a colleague.","label":[[87,126,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2167,"text":"It cost S$5313.17 to repair the damage, which was borne by company ST Synthesis, a services arm of ST Engineering.","label":[[67,79,"ORG"],[99,113,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2170,"text":"On-campus selection may still need to proceed for a small number of courses, where the selection process cannot be meaningfully replicated remotely. For instance, selections for ITE's Nitec in Nursing and Higher Nitec in Performance Production, as well as Nanyang Polytechnic's Diploma in Oral Health Therapy will be conducted on-campus.","label":[[178,181,"ORG"],[256,275,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2171,"text":"The Consumers Association of Singapore (CASE) and Nanyang Polytechnic's Singapore Institute of Retail Studies (NYP-SIRS) signed a memorandum of understanding (MOU) on Friday (Apr 29) for the development of a new CaseTrust accreditation scheme for online businesses.","label":[[4,38,"ORG"],[40,44,"ORG"],[50,69,"ORG"],[71,109,"ORG"],[111,119,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2172,"text":"The scheme, which will be launched in the second half of this year, will help customers to easily identify reliable online merchants, CASE and NYP-SIRS said in a joint press release.","label":[[134,138,"ORG"],[143,151,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2173,"text":"Nanyang Polytechnic (NYP) has launched a diploma course in artificial intelligence (AI) and data engineering that will be co-developed and co-taught by industry professionals and its lecturers.","label":[[0,19,"ORG"],[21,24,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2175,"text":"The course will adopt NYP's Professional Competency model (PCM), which is aimed at mirroring workplace practices instead of the subject-based approach taken by most schools.","label":[[22,25,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2178,"text":"Dr Ettikan Kandasamy Karuppiah, chief technologist for the Asia Pacific South region at California-based Nvidia, said it is working with NYP to develop a module on applied deep learning, as part of the course.","label":[[59,77,"LOC"],[88,98,"LOC"],[105,111,"ORG"],[137,140,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2180,"text":"NYP lecturers will be given access to teaching materials used at Nvidia's Deep Learning Institute.","label":[[0,3,"ORG"],[65,71,"ORG"],[74,97,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2181,"text":"The diploma course, offered under the NYP School of Engineering, will take in its first students next year.","label":[[38,41,"ORG"],[42,63,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2182,"text":"About 300 nurses who are undergoing advanced training at Nanyang Polytechnic (NYP) have been called to return to their hospitals for two weeks from March 7, the Ministry of Health (MOH) on Friday (March 4).","label":[[57,76,"ORG"],[78,81,"ORG"],[161,179,"ORG"],[181,184,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2183,"text":"In response to TODAY's queries, MOH said such a move will allow them to support their colleagues at the frontlines, particularly in areas that are experiencing \"the highest surge in workloads\" such as emergency departments and Covid-19 treatment facilities.","label":[[15,20,"ORG"],[32,35,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2184,"text":"The nursing students are taking Advanced Diploma courses offered by NYP, which are meant for qualified nurses who want to upgrade their skills.","label":[[68,71,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2186,"text":"The SG Healthcare Corps, which includes former healthcare workers and non-healthcare professionals, as well as the Singapore Armed Forces have also been tapped to support Covid-19 operations.","label":[[4,23,"ORG"],[115,137,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2187,"text":"Augmented reality technology to monitor energy usage in real time was among the green solutions displayed at the launch of a Sustainability Experience Centre on Wednesday (Jan 5) at Nanyang Polytechnic, 180 Ang Mo Kio Ave 8, Singapore 569830.","label":[[125,157,"LOC"],[182,201,"LOC"],[203,223,"LOC"],[225,241,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2188,"text":"The centre is a collaboration between NYP and Schneider Electric, and aims to help small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) experience the potential of green technologies at the workplace.","label":[[38,41,"ORG"],[46,64,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2189,"text":"Dr Kan Ee May, lecturer at the Nanyang Polytechnic School of Engineering, noted that the centre hopes to help cash-strapped SMEs adopt such solutions, which can cost as little as $1.50 per plant.","label":[[31,50,"ORG"],[51,72,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2192,"text":"The headquarters, located at 50 Kallang Avenue, will consolidate the company's Singapore operations at four other offices in Changi (15 Changi Business Park Central 1, Singapore 486057), Penjuru (46 Penjuru Lane, Singapore 609206), Ang Mo Kio and Ayer Rajah. It will also serve as the company's first Innovation Hub in Asia.","label":[[29,46,"LOC"],[125,131,"LOC"],[133,166,"LOC"],[168,184,"LOC"],[187,194,"LOC"],[196,211,"LOC"],[213,229,"LOC"],[232,242,"LOC"],[247,257,"LOC"],[319,323,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2194,"text":"Mr Ong was speaking to reporters on Thursday (Nov 26) after he witnessed how soldiers from the 2nd Battalion Singapore Infantry Regiment (2 SIR) were activated to test how they responded to a mock war scenario. The unit in Amoy Quee Camp, which is among several army ground units like the armour and artillery units that have been put on stand by, was activated.","label":[[95,136,"ORG"],[138,143,"ORG"],[223,237,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2196,"text":"Nanyang Polytechnic (NYP) has partnered financial technology (fintech) hub LATTICE80 to offer its students internships during their first two years in school. Mr Joe Seunghyun Cho, CEO of LATTICE80 and chairman of Marvelstone Group, said in a statement: \"Our innovative joint programme will encourage industry-academia collaborations within the fintech industry... to raise awareness and understanding of the emerging field of fintech.","label":[[0,19,"ORG"],[21,24,"ORG"],[75,84,"ORG"],[188,197,"ORG"],[214,231,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2199,"text":"As football took a backseat, Ng started playing games more competitively while he was a student at Nanyang Polytechnic's (NYP) School of Information Technology.","label":[[99,118,"ORG"],[122,125,"ORG"],[127,159,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2201,"text":"After working really hard and scoring 255 for my Primary School Leaving Examination, I was excited to embark on my life in the IP track.","label":[]}
{"id":2203,"text":"It helped Ms Lee, 18, a student at ITE College West's School of Hospitality, emerge tops in the battle against 10 other students.","label":[[35,51,"ORG"],[54,75,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2204,"text":"Designed by 15 students from the Institute of Technical Education (ITE) College Central's School of Design and Media, along with their lecturers and the NDP creative team, each pack came with items such as light sticks, button badges with artwork from the public, colourful visor hats and an LED bracelet that blinks to the tempo of the music.","label":[[33,65,"ORG"],[67,70,"ORG"],[72,87,"ORG"],[90,116,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2205,"text":"Prime Minister Lee Hsien Loong will deliver the National Day Rally speech on Aug 21 at the Institute of Technical Education Headquarters in Ang Mo Kio, the Prime Minister's Office (PMO) said in a statement on Wednesday (May 11).","label":[[91,136,"LOC"],[140,150,"LOC"],[156,179,"ORG"],[181,184,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2206,"text":"He announced that the Manpower Ministry would study how to give delivery workers a more secure future, and that Employment Pass and S Pass criteria would be tightened over time.","label":[[22,39,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2207,"text":"On race, he said the Government intends to enact a Maintenance of Racial Harmony Act, which will consolidate all existing laws to deal with racial issues and also incorporate softer measures that focus on persuasion and rehabilitation.","label":[[21,31,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2208,"text":"PM Lee delivered last year's rally speech in front of 2,000 attendees in a Mediacorp studio, as well as on the Zoom video-conferencing platform, on top of the traditional television and online audiences.","label":[[75,84,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2209,"text":"Instead, PM Lee delivered a major speech to Singaporeans in Parliament in September that year.","label":[[60,70,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2210,"text":"The rally was last held at the ITE College Central campus in 2019.","label":[[31,50,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2212,"text":"From April, close to 400 ITE students will be trained to apply and integrate AI systems under a partnership between ITE and global technology firm Nvidia signed on Wednesday (Jan 19). They will be equipped with industry experience in implementing AI systems, which are crucial to Singapore's goal of transforming its economy with the technology by 2030, said Education Minister Chan Chun Sing at the signing of the partnership agreement on Wednesday.","label":[[25,28,"ORG"],[116,119,"ORG"],[147,153,"ORG"],[280,289,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2213,"text":"Mr Greg Chew, deputy director of the ITE College Central School of Electronics & Info-Comm Technology, said the partnership is expected to benefit up to about 2,000 students in the next three years.","label":[[37,56,"ORG"],[57,101,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2214,"text":"Under the AI Workforce Readiness Programme, these students will meet the growing demand for skilled workers to adopt AI systems, said Mr Chan. He noted that a wide spectrum of skill sets and job roles are necessary to achieve Singapore's national AI strategy, which \"cannot be fulfilled by a single pipeline of university graduates\".","label":[]}
{"id":2218,"text":"There is a number of public transportation close to The Bayshore that residents can make use of. The closest bus stops are located at The Bayshore Condo, The Summit, East Coast Ville, Evergreen Garden, Calvary Ably of God Church and Lagoon View. For those with vehicles, the shopping district located at Changi Business Park can be easily accessed via East Coast Parkway and Pan Island Expressway in 5 to 10 minutes.","label":[[52,64,"LOC"],[134,152,"LOC"],[154,164,"LOC"],[166,182,"LOC"],[184,200,"LOC"],[202,228,"LOC"],[233,244,"LOC"],[304,324,"LOC"],[352,370,"FAC"],[375,396,"FAC"]]}
{"id":2219,"text":"The Spring Cultural Showcase was held by the Singapore Hokkien Huay Kuan (SHHK) in celebration of the Year of the Tiger.","label":[[45,72,"ORG"],[74,78,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2220,"text":"Fifty guests, such as the association's board of governors and committee members, attended the event at the Singapore Hokkien Huay Kuan Cultural Academy at 5 Sennett Road. The Singapore Hokkien Huay Kuan Cultural Academy (SHHKCA) was established by the Singapore Hokkien Huay Kuan following an announcement by PM Lee Hsien Loong in 2012.","label":[[108,152,"LOC"],[156,170,"LOC"],[176,220,"ORG"],[222,228,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2221,"text":"SHHK president Thomas Chua said the association aims to uphold traditions while encouraging innovation and progression with the times.","label":[[0,4,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2222,"text":"\"The SHHK has uplifted the lives of many Singaporeans, not just the Hokkiens or Chinese, but other ethnic groups too, through its support for education and social welfare since 1840 - that's 182 years ago,\" said Mr Lee, who is also Minister-in-charge of Social Services Integration.","label":[[5,9,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2225,"text":"The building that houses the College of Humanities, Arts and Social Sciences (CoHASS) has been named the Singapore Hokkien Huay Kuan Building, while Nanyang Valley, a road adjacent to the Chinese Heritage Centre - the old Nantah Administration Building - will be renamed the Tan Lark Sye Walk.","label":[[29,76,"ORG"],[78,84,"ORG"],[105,141,"LOC"],[149,163,"LOC"],[188,211,"LOC"],[218,252,"LOC"],[275,292,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2226,"text":"A plaque to mark the renaming was unveiled in a ceremony at the College of Humanities, Arts and Social Sciences on Saturday (Oct 19) that was attended by about 300 guests, including Education Minister Ong Ye Kung.","label":[[64,111,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2227,"text":"\"The naming of the Singapore Hokkien Huay Kuan Building and Tan Lark Sye Walk acknowledge the historic contribution of our local communities towards Singapore's tertiary education development,\" said NTU president Subra Suresh.","label":[[19,55,"LOC"],[60,77,"LOC"],[149,158,"LOC"],[199,202,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2230,"text":"Blk 506 onwards heading Bedok Town Secondary School (Westwards towards Jalan Eunos) belongs to Aljunied GRC. Blk 401 onwards and that side of the road all belong to East Coast GRC other than those specified as Fengshan. Borderline is divided between Bedok North Road.","label":[[0,7,"LOC"],[24,51,"LOC"],[71,82,"LOC"],[95,107,"LOC"],[109,116,"LOC"],[165,179,"LOC"],[210,218,"LOC"],[250,266,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2231,"text":"Entire Chai Chee estate (Ping An, Ping Yi, Chai Chee Gardens) is under Tan Chuan Jin's Kembangan ward of Marine Parade GRC. Opposite of Chai Chee estate (Bordered by the MRT track), it was belong Joo Chiat.Longvale (The extremely inside of Bedok Reservoir View, which is next to LTK ward FYI) is under East Coast GRC.","label":[[7,16,"LOC"],[25,32,"LOC"],[34,41,"LOC"],[43,60,"LOC"],[87,96,"LOC"],[105,122,"LOC"],[136,145,"LOC"],[196,205,"LOC"],[206,214,"LOC"],[240,260,"LOC"],[302,316,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2232,"text":"Fengshan SMC comprises these areas Blk 111 - 128 ONLY along the side of Fengshan CC. Bordered by Bedok North St 2. Blk 98 to 110 at Bedok Green Sec cluster. Opposite of it as in Bedok North Ave 3 will facing Aljunied GRC. Blk 74 - 82 side, bordered by Bedok North Road.So Bedok Stadium is under East Coast GRC. Blk 180 - 185, newly BTO right opposite of Bedok Stadium. Simpang Bedok estate from Tanah Merah MRT to the Canal that borders Bedok and Changi \/ Expo.","label":[[0,12,"LOC"],[35,48,"LOC"],[72,83,"LOC"],[97,113,"LOC"],[115,128,"LOC"],[132,147,"LOC"],[178,195,"LOC"],[208,220,"LOC"],[222,233,"LOC"],[252,268,"LOC"],[272,285,"LOC"],[295,309,"LOC"],[311,324,"LOC"],[354,367,"LOC"],[369,382,"LOC"],[395,410,"LOC"],[418,423,"FAC"],[437,442,"LOC"],[447,453,"LOC"],[456,460,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2233,"text":"To add bonus, Lee Yi Shyan as Chai Chee MP do not cover HDB estates with Cha Chee X road name. Instead, it covers the square from Bedok North Ave 3, Bedok North Road & Bedok North Ave 1, effectively circling entire Bedok Central \/ Swimming Pool areas to Fengshan Primary.","label":[[30,39,"LOC"],[73,81,"LOC"],[130,147,"LOC"],[149,165,"LOC"],[168,185,"LOC"],[215,244,"LOC"],[254,270,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2234,"text":"Probably Lim Swee Say is at Bedok Stadium, the few blocks along Bedok North St 2 that are opposite of Fengshan CC (And hence the SMC) and the HDB clusters right opposite of Bedok Point, bounded by Bedok South Ave 1, Bedok South Road and Bedok South Ave 2. (The Blk 16 Hawker there all LSS while Elderhome that side probably Siglap)","label":[[28,41,"LOC"],[64,80,"LOC"],[102,113,"LOC"],[173,184,"LOC"],[197,214,"LOC"],[216,232,"LOC"],[237,254,"LOC"],[257,274,"LOC"],[295,304,"LOC"],[324,330,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2237,"text":"Must eat the bak chor mee (Minced meat noodles) at Kaki Bukit 511. Better than Block 85 Fengshan. Don't know what they put in their soup man. Can request for bigger bowl. Another must try is the Seng Kee Mee Sua.","label":[[51,65,"LOC"],[79,96,"LOC"],[195,211,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2238,"text":"Bouncy fishballs from Yam Mee Teochew Fishball Noodle #01-24, Kaki Bukit Block 511 Market & Food Centre. Branch of the popular fishball noodle stall from Kovan Food Centre with the same name.","label":[[22,53,"ORG"],[62,103,"LOC"],[154,171,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2240,"text":"In a statement on Sunday (June 7), the Ministry of Education (MOE) said all five cases had mild symptoms, and are from Anglican High School, CHIJ Katong Convent, CHIJ St Theresa's Convent, Geylang Methodist Secondary School and Hwa Chong Institution.","label":[[39,60,"ORG"],[119,139,"ORG"],[141,160,"ORG"],[162,187,"ORG"],[189,223,"ORG"],[228,249,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2241,"text":"While the finalists for both events have yet to be determined, the top four from last year have qualified for the semi-finals again with defending champions Victoria School taking on Dunman High School earlier in the week.","label":[[157,172,"ORG"],[183,201,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2243,"text":"The sevens format has not dented the ambitions of heavyweights St Andrew's Secondary (SASS) and Anglo-Chinese School (Independent).","label":[[63,84,"ORG"],[86,90,"ORG"],[96,130,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2244,"text":"Defending champions ACS(I) take on Raffles Institution (RI) in the semi-finals on April 18 while 2019 finalists SASS will play ACS (Barker Road).","label":[[20,26,"ORG"],[35,54,"ORG"],[56,58,"ORG"],[112,116,"ORG"],[127,144,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2245,"text":"After beating two-time defending champions Singapore Chinese Girls' School and finishing top in the preliminary round, Methodist Girls' School are the favourites heading into the finals on April 20.","label":[[43,74,"ORG"],[119,142,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2249,"text":"Eight Temasek Junior College (TJC) staff have been hospitalised for gastroenteritis symptoms after eating food prepared by Chilli Api Catering last Friday (March 12).","label":[[6,28,"ORG"],[30,33,"ORG"],[123,142,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2251,"text":"As the market at Block 85 Bedok North Street 4 was undergoing repair and redecoration works, access control and interim fencing were put in place when it reopened in June.","label":[[17,46,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2252,"text":"Restrictions were lifted this month at markets located at Block 115 Bukit Merah View and Block 137 Tampines Street 11, as well as the Tiong Bahru Market, among others.","label":[[58,84,"LOC"],[89,117,"LOC"],[134,152,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2253,"text":"NEA added that access control and interim fencing had also been removed at 10 other markets earlier in June, including Beo Crescent Market, Bukit Timah Market and Tanglin Halt Market.","label":[[119,138,"LOC"],[140,158,"LOC"],[163,182,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2254,"text":"The four markets are Geylang Serai Market, Chong Pang Market at Block 104\/105 Yishun Road, the market at Block 20\/21 Marsiling Lane and the one at Block 505 Jurong West Street 52.","label":[[21,41,"LOC"],[43,60,"LOC"],[64,89,"LOC"],[105,131,"LOC"],[147,178,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2257,"text":"At Temasek Junior College, Ms Low Ay Nar will make way for Mr Earnler Liu, the current principal of Bowen Secondary School.","label":[[3,25,"ORG"],[100,122,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2258,"text":"At Victoria Junior College, Mr Jeffrey Low will replace Ms Ek Soo Ben, who has been its principal since 2014.","label":[[3,26,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2259,"text":"And with Pioneer Primary School and Juying Primary School merging from 2022, Pioneer Primary's principal Mdm Loke Wai Ling will continue to lead the merged school.","label":[[9,31,"ORG"],[36,57,"ORG"],[77,92,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2261,"text":"The 11 primary schools that will see newly appointed principals are: Anchor Green Primary School, Anglo-Chinese School (Primary), CHIJ (Katong) Primary, Innova Primary School, Kheng Cheng School, Marsiling Primary School, Opera Estate Primary School, Park View Primary School, St Anthony's Primary School, Yew Tee Primary School and Yuhua Primary School.","label":[[69,96,"ORG"],[98,128,"ORG"],[130,151,"ORG"],[153,174,"ORG"],[176,194,"ORG"],[196,220,"ORG"],[222,249,"ORG"],[251,275,"ORG"],[277,304,"ORG"],[306,328,"ORG"],[333,353,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2264,"text":"The property will also appeal to families with school-going children because it is near schools like Temasek Primary, Temasek Secondary and Temasek Junior College. Victoria School and Victoria Junior College are also within 3km of the development.","label":[[101,116,"LOC"],[118,135,"LOC"],[140,162,"LOC"],[164,179,"LOC"],[184,207,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2265,"text":"The cafe is situated at The Yards in Joo Chiat which is a space focusing on arts, dance and drama, on the site of the Old Telok Kurau Primary School at 406 Joo Chiat Place, Singapore 428084","label":[[24,33,"LOC"],[37,46,"LOC"],[118,148,"LOC"],[152,171,"LOC"],[173,189,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2267,"text":"A green space along the Siglap Park Connector, Telok Kurau Park is a great spot for those in the East.","label":[[24,45,"LOC"],[47,63,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2271,"text":"Take the Downtown Line to Kaki Bukit, Exit B.","label":[[9,22,"FAC"],[26,36,"LOC"],[38,44,"FAC"]]}
{"id":2272,"text":"Residents in Eunos will from Friday (Dec 17) have access to a new polyclinic that aside from providing outpatient medical care and treatment for chronic and acute conditions, will also offer radiological services.","label":[[13,18,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2273,"text":"Eunos Polyclinic, the ninth under SingHealth Polyclinics, is located at 1 Chin Cheng Avenue, which is about a 10 minute walk from Eunos MRT station.","label":[[0,16,"LOC"],[34,56,"ORG"],[72,91,"LOC"],[130,147,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2274,"text":"Madam Faridah Mansor is at the Masjid Alkaff Kampung Melayu in Bedok on most days, working from midday to late evening to handle the SafeEntry check-ins of congregants and her responsibilities as the assistant treasurer of the mosque.","label":[[31,59,"LOC"],[63,68,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2276,"text":"He was also a member of MediShield Life Council from 2015 to 2020, and is currently the honorary treasurer of Cerebral Palsy Alliance Singapore and part of the Human Capital Development Panel at the National Council of Social Service.","label":[[24,47,"ORG"],[110,143,"ORG"],[160,191,"ORG"],[199,233,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2278,"text":"Other Bedok Reservoir residents in blocks like Blk 725 Bedok Reservoir Rd, will also have to make a longer journey. Interestingly enough, the block right across the road from Bedok North Block 708, which will have to collect their tokens at Punggol CC, can collect theirs at Eunos CC.","label":[[6,21,"LOC"],[47,73,"LOC"],[175,196,"LOC"],[241,251,"LOC"],[275,283,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2279,"text":"Anybody have their car repaired at Z1 Automotive (1 Kaki Bukit Ave 6, #01-87, Singapore 417883)? The price they quoted for replacement of shock absorber and wheel bearing are very cheap when compared to other workshop.","label":[[35,48,"ORG"],[50,68,"LOC"],[78,94,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2281,"text":"Behind Kembangan Plaza. There's a few food heaven here... You guys should try eating at Hawa Seafood Restaurant...very very Nice !=D","label":[[7,22,"LOC"],[88,111,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2282,"text":"A new lawn and lookout deck in East Coast Park now offers East Coast residents additional space for recreational activities.","label":[[31,46,"LOC"],[58,68,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2283,"text":"\"ABC Waters @ Siglap Canal is an example of innovative use of space at our canals so that vibrant community focal points can be created for communities to gather and bond by the waters,\" said PUB's Chief Sustainability Officer, Mr Tan Nguan Sen.","label":[[14,26,"LOC"],[192,195,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2285,"text":"In 2015, an upstream section of the Siglap Canal near the Kampong Kembangan Community Club (CC) was decked over to create an activity plaza for various community activities.","label":[[36,48,"LOC"],[58,90,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2286,"text":"Besides installing an upgraded covered linkway to provide connectivity options for nearby residents, upgrading works were also done at Telok Kurau Primary School to enable outdoor learning experiences for its students.","label":[[135,161,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2288,"text":"Over her lunch at Braddell Heights CC on Wednesday, Ms Lee, 44, said: \"This is the only place out of public view that we can eat at.","label":[[18,37,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2289,"text":"Fellow ambassador Chan S.K., 44, echoed her sentiments. He has been eating lunch at Braddell Heights CC since Monday.","label":[[84,103,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2291,"text":"Among the Victoria School B Division hockey players, Jangra Aditya is considered a late starter, having taken up the sport only three years ago.","label":[[10,25,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2297,"text":"J8 was an interesting mall next to AMK Estate. I like the restaurants here like Canton Paradise, Dian Xiao Er, Swensens and Ding Tai Fung. Occasionally also meeting friends for coffee here in Ya Kun or Coffeebean or Toastbox. My favourite shop Future State is here too. Also like to watch movies in Golden Village here in J8.","label":[[0,2,"LOC"],[35,45,"LOC"],[80,95,"ORG"],[97,109,"ORG"],[111,119,"ORG"],[124,137,"ORG"],[192,198,"ORG"],[202,212,"ORG"],[216,224,"ORG"],[244,256,"ORG"],[299,313,"ORG"],[322,324,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2298,"text":"Two of the three new Covid-19 clusters announced yesterday involve 22 people, including 16 staff, at the Bishan and Sengkang bus interchanges, said the Ministry of Health (MOH).","label":[[105,111,"LOC"],[116,140,"LOC"],[152,170,"ORG"],[172,175,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2300,"text":"SBS Transit said in a statement on Saturday night that about 97 per cent of its bus captains have been vaccinated as at Aug 12.","label":[[0,11,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2301,"text":"Meanwhile, My First Skool at 54 Chin Swee Road had five additional cases on Saturday, bringing its total to 17 cases.","label":[[11,25,"ORG"],[29,46,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2304,"text":"After closing briefly for a facelift, Bishan's popular Kim San Leng Kopitiam will soon reopen for business. The revamped coffeeshop also houses two new famous stall tenants, Chef Wei HK Cheong Fun and King of Fried Rice, which are opening tomorrow (Dec 23).","label":[[38,44,"LOC"],[55,76,"ORG"],[174,196,"ORG"],[201,219,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2305,"text":"Seeking witness for this bicycle accident. Happened on 5\/6\/21 (Saturday). Location: Running track (Bishan Park Connector) behind Kuo Chuan Presbyterian Secondary School","label":[[99,120,"LOC"],[129,168,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2307,"text":"Proceeds from the carnival will be split equally to the school's six partner beneficiaries - HCA Hospice Care, Movement for the Intellectually Disabled of Singapore, Presbyterian Community Services, Bishan Home for the Intellectually Disabled, Lions Home for the Elders and Reach Community Services Society.","label":[[93,109,"ORG"],[111,164,"ORG"],[166,197,"ORG"],[199,242,"ORG"],[244,269,"ORG"],[274,306,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2315,"text":"The Bishan Community Club is also home to many chess federatioms, which organises courses for learners.","label":[[4,25,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2316,"text":"A woman, accused of not wearing a mask at Shunfu Mart near Upper Thomson Road was charged in the district court on Tuesday (May 5) with one count of being a public nuisance and three counts of violating Covid-19 rules.","label":[[42,53,"LOC"],[59,77,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2318,"text":"The project, on Shunfu Road, is located within a short walking distance of the Marymount MRT station on the Circle Line.","label":[[16,27,"LOC"],[79,100,"LOC"],[108,119,"FAC"]]}
{"id":2319,"text":"According to Qingjian, the project will be the first residential development to adopt a","label":[[13,21,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2320,"text":"The design architect of JadeScape is Japanese architect Paul Noritake Tange, chairman of Tange Associates. Recent projects in Singapore designed by the renowned architectural firm include One Raffles Place Tower 2; Orchard Gateway, which features a bridge spanning across Orchard Road; and The Rochester, a mixed-use development at one-north.","label":[[24,33,"LOC"],[89,105,"ORG"],[126,135,"LOC"],[188,213,"LOC"],[215,230,"LOC"],[272,284,"LOC"],[290,303,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2321,"text":"Kong Meng San Phor Kark See Monastery is the largest Buddhist temple in Singapore, and I would argue that it's probably the most beautiful Buddhist temple in the country.","label":[[0,37,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2322,"text":"The monastery is located 88 Bright Hill Rd, Singapore 574117, next to Bright Hill MRT Station Exit 2.","label":[[25,42,"LOC"],[44,60,"LOC"],[70,93,"LOC"],[94,100,"FAC"]]}
{"id":2325,"text":"With the gradual opening of our nation in phase 3 of the battle against the pandemic, we are happy to announce that residents can start using the Eunoia JC facilities on the weekends: (1) the elevated track on top of Marymount CC (2) indoor courts for more badminton slots and (3) outdoor field for those that love frisbee.","label":[[146,155,"LOC"],[217,229,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2328,"text":"Casuarina Curry at 136 Casuarina Road is hugely popular among the morning breakfast crowd for several good reasons.","label":[[0,15,"ORG"],[19,37,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2329,"text":"Though not the best we've tasted, they are the only Vietnamese joint in the whole of Upper Thomson. Address: 215M Upper Thomson Road","label":[[85,98,"LOC"],[108,132,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2330,"text":"Nestled in the Sembawang Hills Estate neighbourhood at 4 Jalan Kuras is Thus Coffee, a chic cafe that offers stellar grain bowls, pasta, brunch, hearty stews and coffee.","label":[[15,37,"LOC"],[55,68,"LOC"],[72,83,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2332,"text":"A massive fire in a Jurong industrial area raged for more than two hours and triggered loud explosions on Friday (June 21), killing one and leaving two people injured.","label":[[20,26,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2335,"text":"In 2015, he took up a grant by Tuas Power Generation to study at NUS School of Engineering, today the NUS College of Design & Engineering","label":[[31,52,"ORG"],[65,68,"ORG"],[69,90,"ORG"],[102,105,"ORG"],[106,137,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2336,"text":"The Transocean Norge rig was built by Sembcorp Marine at the Tanjong Kling Shipyard in Singapore between 2012 and 2016.","label":[[38,53,"ORG"],[61,83,"LOC"],[87,96,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2337,"text":"After Sembmarine has consolidated its operations at its integrated Tuas Boulevard Yard, the group is expected to realise cost savings estimated at SGD48m per annum from its financial year 2020.","label":[[6,16,"ORG"],[67,86,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2338,"text":"The Singapore Food Agency (SFA) said on Friday (Oct 22) it is investigating Catering Solutions over meals it provided to residents of Westlite Jalan Tukang Dormitory at 11A Jalan Tukang.","label":[[4,25,"ORG"],[27,30,"ORG"],[76,94,"ORG"],[134,165,"LOC"],[169,185,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2344,"text":"Long waiting time for red zone patients (those w cough\/flu\/fever) at Bukit batok Polyclinic...need to queue to register despite making an appointment the night before and registering in advance on the Health Hub app.","label":[[69,91,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2345,"text":"We send a parcel to Pakistan via Singapore Post Bukit Batok Central Branch 1 Bukit Batok Central Link, #05-09 West Mall, Singapore 658713, on 21 December 2020, at 16:58 hrs, consisting of 2 Uniqlo Sweaters, worth SGD39.90 and SGD 19.90.","label":[[33,47,"ORG"],[48,74,"LOC"],[75,101,"LOC"],[110,119,"LOC"],[121,137,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2347,"text":"West Mall is accessible from 8am onwards, and post office should be open along with other brands such as Cold Storage etc. Let them redeliver or redirect to Westgate. Post Office is a Service Provider and should meet residents needs.","label":[[0,9,"LOC"],[157,165,"LOC"],[167,178,"FAC"]]}
{"id":2348,"text":"Bukit batok Bus Interchange next to West Mall, Bukit Batok MRT station with plenty of shopping banking local Int'l delights supermarkets entertainment and amenities including cinemas library and Bukit Batok community club.","label":[[0,27,"LOC"],[36,45,"LOC"],[47,70,"LOC"],[195,221,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2351,"text":"Bought itea.sg new mango sago pomelo from their Tiong Bahru Plaza branch and found extra ingredient inside. Notified them on Facebook but no respond.","label":[[7,14,"ORG"],[48,65,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2353,"text":"Don't understand what a 24hr coffee shop is for?! Lights off at 11pm, fans off at 11pm when customer are still all around? Then what do you call yourself a 24hr it's coffee shop for?! Might as well just close off and don't open at night? Who is the one incharge?! Just work for the sake of working?! How do the customer even continue eating??? NTUC FairPrice what is this??? 476D Upper Serangoon View","label":[[344,358,"ORG"],[375,400,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2355,"text":"Met a ridiculous cyclist this morning (20th May 2022 at 09.37am) on Stevens Road, I was driving along Stevens Road and turning left into Anderson Road, while I was turning, a cyclist continued to cycle on the pedestrian despite the light was red, to make it worst, he kicked my car when he cycled past me.","label":[[68,80,"LOC"],[102,114,"LOC"],[137,150,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2356,"text":"Chain collision happen on 20\/05\/22 at about 12:26pm in the afternoon. Incident happen at Ang Mo Kio Ave 1.","label":[[89,105,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2357,"text":"Rodents infestation at behind Blk 10 Telok Blangah Cresent.","label":[[30,58,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2358,"text":"WC Tham is at Blk 6 Tanjong Pagar Plaza Hawker Centre. Loading\/Unloading Lot Became Private Parking Lot..!!?","label":[[14,53,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2359,"text":"Very disgusting and smelly every day need to pass by this area, and I can not believe this is Singapore HDB flat, the dustbin area just next to the lift that we need to take everyday. Tanjong Pagar Town Council, can u do something about this, Block 37 Jalan Rumah Tinggi.","label":[[184,210,"ORG"],[243,270,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2360,"text":"There is this new restaurant Yum Yum Mookata inside this building on level 1 at 2019 Bukit Batok Industrial Estate Park A .","label":[[29,44,"ORG"],[80,121,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2362,"text":"Guys from International French School Singapore fighting with boxing gloves in public void deck now at Blk 157 Serangoon North Ave 1.","label":[[10,47,"ORG"],[103,132,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2364,"text":"Hi sir, I am reporting a very serious mosquito breeding at Blk 79 Indus Rd S(161079).which might lead to a dengue fever cluster.","label":[[59,84,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2365,"text":"On Monday 9th May, we parked our car at Ang Mo Kio Ind Park 1, near to Block 4008 from morning 9am to evening 7:30pm.","label":[[40,61,"LOC"],[71,81,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2367,"text":"An Fire incident happening on the 15\/05\/22 at 12am. SCDF were Alerted and put off The pire at Blk 180C Marsiling Road. Three persons were conveyed to KK Women's and Children's Hospital","label":[[52,56,"ORG"],[94,117,"LOC"],[150,184,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2368,"text":"Anchorvale McDonald's Runs out of muffin bun for breakfast.. staff didnt inform me also","label":[[0,10,"LOC"],[11,21,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2370,"text":"The incident happen at 261 Serangoon Central Dr and involved the KED of a Coffee Shop on the ground floor of the blk.","label":[[23,47,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2372,"text":"Get Together Coffee Shop (177 Bukit Batok West Avenue 8, Singapore 650177 )is located 15 minutes away by bus from Bukit Batok MRT Station, which is unfortunately not very convenient. However, if you live in the West, this beats travelling halfway across Singapore to satisfy your hawker cravings!","label":[[0,24,"LOC"],[26,55,"LOC"],[57,73,"LOC"],[114,137,"LOC"],[254,263,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2375,"text":"The 36th confirmed case had attended a business meeting at Grand Hyatt Singapore (10 Scotts Road), the same meeting as Cases 30 and 39, as well as several cases overseas. She had not travelled to China recently but had been in Johor Bahru from Jan 25 to Jan 28. The woman also visited a family member at Ng Teng Fong General Hospital prior to her admission and lived at Bukit Batok St 31. On Jan 24, she reported onset of symptoms and visited a GP clinic on Feb 1. She was admitted to KK Women's and Children's Hospital on Feb 4.","label":[[59,80,"LOC"],[82,96,"LOC"],[196,201,"LOC"],[227,238,"LOC"],[304,333,"LOC"],[370,387,"LOC"],[485,519,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2376,"text":"The 37th confirmed case is a private-hire driver with no links to previous cases or recent travel history to China. He reported symptoms on Jan 30 and visited two GP clinics on Feb 1 and Feb 3. On Feb 6, he was admitted to Ng Teng Fong General Hospital. He tested positive on Feb 7 and was transferred to NCID the next day. He lives at Jurong East St 32.","label":[[109,114,"LOC"],[223,252,"LOC"],[305,309,"LOC"],[336,353,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2377,"text":"The 38th case had visited The Life Church and Missions Singapore in Paya Lebar, which is also linked to Cases 8, 9, 31 and 38. She had no recent travel history to China. On Feb 3, she reported the onset of symptoms and visited Choa Chu Kang Polyclinic the next day. She was admitted to NCID on Feb 7, and tested positive for the infection a day later. Prior to hospital admission, she had also visited Marina Bay Sands, Chinatown and Plaza Singapura and had travelled by public transport. She lives at Choa Chu Kang Ave 3.","label":[[26,64,"LOC"],[68,78,"LOC"],[163,168,"LOC"],[227,251,"LOC"],[286,290,"LOC"],[402,418,"LOC"],[420,429,"LOC"],[434,449,"LOC"],[502,521,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2378,"text":"He lives in Jurong West Central. On Feb 16, MOH said that the man has fully recovered from the infection and has been discharged from hospital.","label":[[12,31,"LOC"],[44,47,"ORG"]]}
{"id":2379,"text":"The man then sought treatment at Hougang Polyclinic on Feb 6 and at Tan Tock Seng Hospital on Feb 7. Prior to hospital admission, he had visited Paya Lebar Methodist Church at 5 Boundary Road and attended a gathering at Braddell Heights Residents' Committee. He also picked up his grandchild outside Pat's Schoolhouse Kovan in Upper Serangoon Road.","label":[[33,51,"LOC"],[68,90,"LOC"],[145,172,"LOC"],[176,191,"LOC"],[220,257,"LOC"],[300,323,"LOC"],[327,347,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2380,"text":"He reported symptoms on Feb 1 and sought treatment at a GP clinic on Feb 3, before going to Changi General Hospital (CGH) on Feb 5. He then went for a follow-up appointment at Bedok Polyclinic on Feb 7 and was admitted to the intensive care unit at CGH. Prior to hospital admission, he had visited Mustafa Centre and stayed at Leo Dormitory at 25 Kaki Bukit Road.","label":[[92,115,"LOC"],[117,120,"LOC"],[176,192,"LOC"],[249,252,"LOC"],[298,312,"LOC"],[327,340,"LOC"],[344,362,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2382,"text":"The 44th case is a Certis Cisco officer who served quarantine orders on two people from Wuhan. He went to Khoo Teck Puat Hospital on Feb 6, where he was isolated and warded. He tested positive for the coronavirus on Feb 9. He works at the Certis Cisco Centre at 20 Jalan Afifi in Paya Lebar, and has no recent travel history to China. Prior to being admitted to hospital, he had been on duty at Chingay 2020. Chingay took place on Jan 31 and Feb 1.","label":[[19,31,"ORG"],[88,93,"LOC"],[106,129,"LOC"],[239,258,"LOC"],[262,276,"LOC"],[280,290,"LOC"],[328,333,"LOC"]]}
{"id":2383,"text":"The 45th case, a two-year-old girl, was among the 92 Singaporeans evacuated from Wuhan on Jan 30. She did not have symptoms when she boarded the flight, and was put under quarantine after landing in Singapore. She was referred to KK Women's and Children's Hospital on Feb 7 based on initial test results and isolated.","label":[[81,86,"LOC"],[199,208,"LOC"],[230,264,"LOC"]]}
